<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="e_s_disc">

        <item>Established in 1965, Gaylord is one of the iconic restaurants in South Mumbai. This eatery is very old and is known for its North Indian and Continental cuisine.</item>
        <item>If you want a good dining experience with your family or friends, Umame is the place where you should head to. They offer a great variety of Asian cuisine.</item>
        <item>Superb place to have some Mughlai and mouthwatering spicy Chinese cuisines. Moreover you will also find some interesting pizzas at this place at very affordable rates.</item>
        <item>One of the oldest restaurants of Mumbai, Noor Mohammadi Hotel is right place to enjoy some great variety in non vegetarian delights. Chicken lovers put your shoes.</item>
        <item>Symphony a family restaurant and bar, popular among South Mumbai folks who often checkout this place for a decent dinner. They serve Indian, Chinese and Continental cuisines.</item>
        <item>This place is popular for a dish called as \'Kepsa\', It is a dish made with combination of chicken tikka and chicken fried rice. You get it in large quantity.</item>
        <item>Taste of Kerla, is a quick trip to Kerala. They serve amazing and authentic South Indian food. This place is quite known for \'Sadya\', google it if you don\'t know.</item>
        <item>Head to this place if you want to explore a tasty combination of tandoori and schezwan flavours. The mouth-watering dish Chicken Leg Schezwan Tandoori is worth trying.</item>
        <item>Shawarma lovers if you are in Grant Road you can\'t miss this place. They serve fresh chicken shawarma loaded with lots of cheese. You will love this place and taste.</item>
        <item>An ideal place to get perfect quality, perfect quantity, perfect taste and just perfect price. It\s very perfect and you will agree with this if you go here.</item>
        <item>This place is a perfect place to organize a party, otherwise the food you get is very tasty and every time you will find changes in their menu with more unique dishes added.</item>
        <item>A good place to enjoy non vegetarian delights in Byculla without giving any tipe of burden to your wallet. It is a street food joint with indoor seating area.</item>
        <item>From Chinese to Indian they serve a range of food delights you would love to eat. Nice and cosy place, you will surely bring your family with you if you come here.</item>
        <item>A popular seafood joint n Lower Parel, Jai Hind Lunch Home offers you fresh and tasty varieties of fish. This place is quite small in size but the food you get makes up for it.</item>
        <item>One of the rare Irani Restaurant in heart of the city, Cafe Colony is good place to have a quick Irani chai with a kheema pav. It\'s a small crowded place with good food!</item>
        <item>A budget chinese stop in Parel, they serve lip smaking chinese chicken recipes. This place is quite small in size but the food the serves is mouth-watering.</item>
        <item>If you want to eat some authentic Goan and Malvani seafood with complete satisfaction and loud burp, you shoud definitely head to Diva Maharashtracha in Dadar.</item>
        <item>Bombay Burgers serves some good quality hot and tasty burgers. A good place to hangout with friends and enjoy lip-smacking crispy and crunchy burgers in Wadala.</item>
        <item>Irani Restaurant in Wadala, they offer a range of Irani food items and even known for some chinese dishes. The staff is not good but the food is what we are concerned with.</item>
        <item>Raj Palace Restaurant has a take away section outside where you get something delicious. Chicken Tandoori, Mutton Kebabs, Chicken Tikka and what not! Don\'t go mad.</item>
        <item>If you are yet to visit this place and you think you have had the best \'Paya\' dish, you are completely wrong. The paya soup you get here is awesome and affordable too!</item>
        <item>Hangout spot of Ruia College students, China Man Restaurant is known for mouth-watering momos at affordable rates. Also give a try for chicken lolipop here.</item>
        <item>Not so good ambience, not so good hygiene and still you are mad when it comes to eating Mughlai food you should head to this places. Try their chicken servings! </item>
        <item>Not so good place to have a seat and eat when we talk about hygiene and ambience but the food you get here is real gold. Check out some kebabs and chicken servings. </item>
        <item>Sea food lovers in somewhere in Chembur should checkout this place for sure. Hotel Navina offers a range of South Indian and mouth-watering sea foods delights in Chembur</item>
        <item>The Sindh Punjab Dhaba offers Punjabi, Sindhi and Koliwada cuisines. It has open kitchen and the walls decorated with posters of bollywood actors. Good ambience and good food!</item>
        <item>One of the best places in Vikroli to hangout with your loved ones. It\'s a big and spacious restaurant which offers good quality food in good quantity as well!</item>
        <item>Shangai Express serves quality Chinese cuisines at great prices. You might need to wait before you get a place to sit, since this restaurant is quite small but food is amazing.</item>
        <item>Hotel Malvan Samudra, their name is enough to give an idea about what they serve. You get some authentic fish, chicken and mutton dishes at reasonable rates. Fish feast place!</item>
        <item>Chinese lovers in Thane are often spotted at this place. Silly Chilly is where you get authentic chinese cuisines. You get both veg and non-veg delights but it is known for biryani!</item>
        <item>Safe Caterers in Bandra is where you get tasty biryani. They serve a good variety of biryanis along with other chicken and mutton dishes like mutton samosa and much more.</item>
        <item>This place might lack fancy interiors and superb service but what it has is some lip-smacking chicken dishes. Best part is it is light on your pocket. Good food at less price!</item>
        <item>Chinese lovers this is your destination if you are somewhere between Khar and Santacruz. The serve tasty and good variety of veg and non-veg Chinese cuisine.</item>
        <item>Quality and quantity both the factors are satisfied at this eatery. The Al Zaika Fast Food is a great place to munch some snacks on the go while taking care of your wallet.</item>
        <item>Non vegetarian street food is at it\'s best at Hot Seekh in Santacruz. This goto streetside meat spot offers a range of shawarmas, kebabs, tikkas and what not!</item>
        <item>If you want to enjoy authentic South Indian cuisine served in Banana Leaf and you are in Santacruz you should definitely head to this place. They also serve tasty fish.</item>
        <item>Amazing bakery in Santacruz, they serve quality bakery products. Some of the most popular bakery items are pattice, plum cakes, brownies, mawa cake and much more!</item>
        <item>Very few people know about this place, Harish Lunch Home in Vile Parle serves authentic Mangalorean cuisine. Sea food lovers note down this place and head to  ultimate destination.</item>
        <item>The Avenue in Kandivali offers great quality North Indian and Chinese cuisines. If you love gazals, you should check out this place and enjoy tasty meal with your favourite gazals.</item>
        <item>Popularly known as \'Biryani King Of Mumbai\', Jaffer Bhai\'s Delhi Darbar established in 1973 still stands tall when it comes to producing best biryani of Mumbai.</item>
        <item>Bombay Duck not being a duck but lizardfish, is one of the iconic things to eat in Mumbai. But wait, where to eat? Ofcourse at any outlet of Gomantak, as simple as that!</item>
        <item>Goila Butter Chicken-\'Ratio and Proportion at its best!\' Chicken to Gravy, Sweet to Spicy and Onion to Tomato. They are just perfect at their calculations. </item>
        <item>Good place to try crispy and tasty chicken lolipops in the city. It has superb ambience and seating area. All in all, it is fantastic place to catch up. </item>
        <item>If you love eating rolls and wraps, if you have some unconditional love with sea food, believe me or not this is your place. Ultimate place for fish lovers.</item>
        <item>Home Chef All Day Dining is cozy cafe in Dadar, they offer some good quality snacks and variety of cakes. Check out spicy and hot Chicken 65 here, you will love it!</item>
        <item>The owners of this chain are of Tibetan origin, so making delicious momos is their cup of tea. The restaurant is ery tiny but the taste of their food is unmatched.</item>
        <item>Hotel Malvan Samudra as their name says, if you are craving for authentic Malvani food delight you can\'t afford to remove this place from your list. Check out now!</item>
        <item>One of the popular food chains of Bandra since last 17 years is this place, known for delicious shawarma. Extensive range of shawarma will keep you wondering what to try.</item>
        <item>It is a real gem in the crowd of so many food joints around, if you are eager to eat a bhurji pav. Irani chai and a bhurji pav at this place will take you to heaven. </item>
        <item>One of Bandra\'s most popular Irani cafes, Good Luck offers some delicious omelettes in the city. A perfect place to take a break and get tasty breakfast on the go.</item>
        <item>At Hotel Sindhudurg you will get to taste some authentic Malvani dishes. Try Surmai Malvani curry, Surmai or King Fish is popular fish in Malvani Restaurants. </item>
        <item>If you are looking for homely ambience and authentic Malvani food, this restaurant is made for you. Chaitanya offers Malvani delight while taking care of your wallet.</item>
        <item>If you want a biryani in best proportion of rice to meat to masala, you have left with this option. They offer multiple options and varieties of biryani, don\'t get confused.</item>
        <item>About 45 years ago, a guy borrowed some money from his friend and started this wonderful place. Many things might have changed but one thing is constant, the taste of bombil.</item>
        <item>They are the first to bring the concept of butter chicken in Mumbai, way back in 1942! An interesting ambience and decor with interesting food, the taste you won\'t forget.</item>
        <item>Apple chicken is their speciality. They turn an ordinary chicken lolipop into heaven, the taste you will remember for years and bring you back to this place again and again.</item>
        <item>Populated with food lovers, its difficult to find this place vacant. You are likely to get addicted to this place if you try their chicken roti and other food items once.</item>
        <item>You are not a true momo fan if you are yet to visit this place. This is the perfect location to explore variety of momos specially the chicken and egg varieties.</item>
        <item>You will find number of restaurants in Powai but when you talk about eating mouth-watering Malvani food you can\'t forget Soul Curry. Kombi Vade at it\'s best!</item>
        <item>As the name says, this place manufactures world-class Shawarmas in your city. Along with lip smaking shawarmas this place also has some indoor games and books to read.</item>
        <item>This place serves a variety of egg dishes. The cost is little higher but the food served here is worth it. This place is a paradise for egg lovers in the city.</item>
        <item>This old cafe is heaven for Parsi style food lovers. Wake up early, head to this amazing place and grab a cup of popular Irani tea along with an omelette. </item>
        <item>One of the most popular seafood outlets in the city, Gajalee stands for what it is today. The sea food they offer is outstanding. A complete package for the sea foodies.</item>
        <item>A 79 year old restaurant which started with just 7 dishes on their menu, today it is one of the popular biryani hotspots in the city. Vegans might get something interesting too.</item>
        <item>Inspired by the Konkan coast of Maharashtara and located at the heart of Mumbai, this place is the perfect place to try some lip-smaking fish dishes specially the Bombil fry.</item>
        <item>Enjoy their creamy butter chicken with chur chur naan, and praise us later. Book a table in advance or prepare yourself to wait it out, such is the hype of this place. </item>
        <item>If you believe in rumours, then this are the guys who brought the concept of chicken lolipop in Mumbai. Respect them and taste this food at their place, you won\'t regret.</item>
        <item>This is a small stall with tasty rolls, popularly known for burnt garlic chicken roll. Kathi Kebab Roll is really a hidden jewel, add it to your bucket list!</item>
        <item>Kaitlyn\'s Beer Garden in Bandra is a pub and bar. It has a indoor garden decor and they play live music while you have some good quality taty and mind-boggling meal.</item>
        <item>You cant call it just a hut when it is located in south Bombay, it is an heavenly place for momo lovers around the world. Enjoy the beautiful view of sea while you eat.</item>
        <item>Malvan Tadka in Thane is where Malvani sea foodat it\'s best. They also offer North Indian and Chinese cuisine but the Malvani food stands out of all. Enjoy spicy seafood!</item>
        <item>Explore some amazing shawarmas and satisfy your greedy soul at this place. This place also serves various other Lebanese dishes and ensures there is no hole in your pocket!</item>
        <item>Relax and order a chai and a bhurji pav, this vintage 90 years old cafe will take you back into the retro era. Enjoy the vibes along with a tasty bhurji pav! </item>
        <item>If you want to explore something unique along with omelette, this is the place. They turn tasty omelette into a tasty plus healthy omelette, try Greek salad omelette.</item>
        <item>Another iconic seafood restaurant of Mumbai, which offers iconic seafood. The \'gassi\' at Apoorva is a nice balance of chilly and tanginess. Enjoy authentic seafood here!</item>
        <item>Mahesh Lunch Home serves authentic Manglorean cuisine in the city. The thick prawn curry, bombil fry, appam and dosa is what you should die for at this crazy food outlet.</item>
        <item>Being in this \'Biryani Business\' for last 94 years, their Biryani turns out to be a winner as Eid feasts go. You will find a resahmi white masala base instead of the red one.</item>
        <item>Being populated by food enthusiasts daily and popular for its homely and cosy ambiance this is the place for you if you wish to taste red coconut chutney with crispy bombil. </item>
        <item>Your body might be somewhere in Mumbai but your heart might be in some dhaba of Punjab, such is the taste of butter chicken at Punjab Grills.</item>
        <item>A small place with a big menu card, place to explore variety of chicken dishes. It is a quick stop to satisfy your hungry soul with tasty chicken lolipop and other varieties.</item>
        <item>Tibbs is a popular name when it comes to frankies. They have vast variety, it is quite normal for you to get confused. Select any you won\'t regret for sure! </item>
        <item>3 Wise Monkeys in Khar is a pub and eatery with old world charm. It is a great place to enjoy karaoke and live music while having tasty and lip-smacking non vegetarian delights</item>
        <item>Here you will find an excellent collection of momos - veg, non-veg, fried, steamed. Check out their steamed chicken momos and don\'t forget to ask for extra red chutney!</item>
        <item>Amcho Koliwado offers traditional Malvani food. It\'s a small place with interesting decor and great service. The seafood and chicken dishes are at their best here!</item>
        <item>You don\'t need to be a King to be at King\'s Shawarma, a pocket friendly location to enjoy a big range of lip smacking shawarmas in your city.</item>
        <item>A small joint in Goregaon serving delicious bhurji pav since last 30 years. The egg bhurji you get here is simply lip smacking and the taste will bring you back again.</item>
        <item>Another Irani cafe you shoud check out to satisfy your greedy soul. They offer omellets, fried eggs, brun muska and special Irani chai. Worth visiting place!</item>
        <item>If you need something different than the traditional style biryani, this is the perfect place for you. Exclusively explore the concept of \'Chicken Tikka Biryani\'</item>
        <item>Offering an array of seafood varieties, this is one of the places to check out bombil fry. Crispy bombil fry and a glass of cool sol kadi, a perfect combination!</item>
        <item>Again, one of the oldest chains in the city to offer lip-smaking Butter chicken to staisfy your soul. Perfect place to hangout with family and friends.</item>
        <item>The best thing about chicken lolipop is you don\'t need to always go to a restaurant to taste this heaven, sometimes check out some bakeries too and get surprised!</item>
        <item>Right place to enjoy softest and most delicious mutton rolls in the city at unbelievable price. The other options and varieties will also make you go mad.</item>
        <item>Hoppumm in Bandra is a great place to dine-out with your family for a non-vegetarian food feast. If you want to taste Sri Lankan cuisine you should check-out here.</item>
        <item>Tandoori momos of Bhukkha Sher are getting more and more popular in the city. The quality and quantity of stuffing is just perfect and will definitely bring you back.</item>
        <item>Food N Flame is a very small place in Andheri, they serve lip-smacking sea food and North Indian dishes. The Kombi Vade you get here are mind-boggling, you will be back here!</item>
        <item>This juice center is not juice center, it is one of the popular shawarma destinations of Mumbai. Other tasty food items here will also give you a reason to visit this place again.</item>
        <item>Perfect location for a quick pocket friendly bhurji pav breakfast. The Irani style cafe is popular among the college students. Right place for a quick bhurji pav bite.</item>
        <item>Bagel shop is right location not just to taste some delicious bagel in the city but also omelette and egg dishes. It is a pet friendly place, so take them with you!</item>
        <item>This place is a hidden treasure in the city, a small place quite difficult to find. But as soon as you reach this place the food is worth the hard work you do to get here.</item>
        <item>A small place with quick service, Jai Hind Lunch Home is where you get best fish dishes you ever had. Sea food lovers cannot afford to miss this superb place in Bandra.</item>
        <item>Very popular amongst students and working folks, Raju Sandwich Stall at Churchgate is where you should head to have some lip-smacking authentic street food.</item>
        <item>The Churchgate Khau galli is a small lane with lots of Mumbai\'s favourite food. This place is heaven for all the foodies in the city. It is the street food feast.</item>
        <item>If you think Mumbai is all about non-vegetarian food, vegetarian food is a myth here. Then it\s the time to think again. Just head to this place to prove yourself wrong.</item>
        <item>Shree Sai Fast Food is where spiciness is at it\'s peak. Enjoy some hot and spicy pulav at this place. If you love spicy food and masala in your food this is the place.</item>
        <item>Head off this place if you need some calmness in the hot streets of Mumbai. The refreshing drink seems to be a gola in form of a drink made with fresh watermelon.</item>
        <item>This place is where the combination of food is always at its best. A unique blend of South Indian and Chinese cuisine is found here. Fusion dosa at its best.</item>
        <item>A quick place to grab some Kanda Bhajiya and continue your daily routine. This place is the right location to grab some quick food and calm down your hunger.</item>
        <item>A tiny shop with a big banner \'King Of Mawa Jalebi\' and they are very correct with this banner. Unlike normal jalebis, you should give a try to yummy mawa jalebis!</item>
        <item>Masala Milk At Noorani Milk Center is the medicine to beat the heat while roaming in hot streets of Mumbai. They serve this milk in small packed cute bottles.</item>
        <item>One of the popular sweet outlet in South Mumbai, this is the right stop to grab some sweet and turn yourself in to a sweet person. The sweets made here are of pure ghee.</item>
        <item>Crystal Restaurant near Wilson College, established around 100 years ago is where vegetarian foodies should park their cars. THis place serves lip smacking North Indian Cuisines.</item>
        <item>The red and white sauce mixed at with perfection to get some thing new and tasty called as Pink Pasta. This pasta is quite popular, you know about it if you live in South Mumbai.</item>
        <item>Explore a new variety in traditional Maggi only at Say Cheese. They add variety of other sauces and cook something you would go mad at. You will be back at this place again.</item>
        <item>As their name says, get ready to taste some thing crazy at this place. Ulta pizza is a combination of two pizza where one pizza is placed ulta over the other.</item>
        <item>Ghee lovers rush to this place. Bhagat Tarachand is where your food is literally dipped in ghee before serving you. This is a perfect restaurant for vegetarians.</item>
        <item>One of the popular khau gallis in the city, this khau galli in Marine Lines has lot to offer. From South Indian to Chinese this is the place to enjoy real Mumbai food.</item>
        <item>Pejas in Grant Road is the right place to have a tasty pizza treat with pocket friendly rates. With abundant cheese and mouth-watering taste, you are always in profit here.</item>
        <item>Beat the heat with a glass of cool kesar lassi at Paradise Milk Center. The lassi is very rich when it comes to its flavour and the dry fruits make it more tasty.</item>
        <item>Small little place with tasty breads, cakes, brownies and cookies. Their cookies stand out of all other things they serve. Soft and mouth-melting cookies only here!</item>
        <item>A fine dining restaurant with beautiful atmosphere and with great inside and outside seating area. A quite place to enjoy some a great meal with your family and friends.</item>
        <item>Vegetarians will love this place, they serve some authentic South Indian food. The food is very tasty and reasonably priced. Sambar and Masala Dosa is at it\s best!</item>
        <item>A place to have a quick Chinese and Indian fusion snacks. It is very hygienic location where you get mouthwatering delights and it\'s a very pocket friendly too! </item>
        <item>A small space with cosy ambience, 1Tablespoon Pizza Kitchen serves international style pizzas with fresh toppings. Best place for quality food at affordable rates.</item>
        <item>This place is also for meat lovers, but the vegetarian food you get here is also worth trying. A perfect place to have some good time with your corporate colleagues.</item>
        <item>A quite place with some excellent decor and ambience to calm your body and mind. It might be heavy on your wallet, but the food they offer is equally good. </item>
        <item>Le 15 Patisserie in Parel, is bit difficult to find but is a good place to have some quick desserts in the city. They offer a good varieties of cupcakes, pastries and macrons.</item>
        <item>Bread and cookies are at their best at this place in Prabhadevi, they serve some good range of tasty breads and cookies which you won\'t find anywhere else in the city.</item>
        <item>A pure vegetarian restaurant in busy streets of Dadar, Hotel Suprabha gives you a homely feel with every bite of food you take at this place. Good quality food at great prices!</item>
        <item>Merwans is very popular name and most of us know about it, they serve good quality fresh cakes with amazing taste. You get mouth-melting cakes at this place!</item>
        <item>This place is always crowded, located at ground floor of Nakshatra Mall at Dadar. They serve some good quality snacks with excellent taste, Dosa here stands out!</item>
        <item>Right place to have some authentic Maharashtrian food in Dadar. Just go here have some quick bites and get back to your work this is how it works. Amazing foooood!</item>
        <item>Gypsy Corner in Dadar is where you get amazing and authentic Maharashtrian cuisine at pocket friendly rates. You get other food varieties too, like pani puri and pavbhaji.</item>
        <item>Vada Pav with spicy schezwan chutney and melting cheese, this sounds good but it tastes best. Amazing flavour and good quality is what makes vada pav at this place special.</item>
        <item>Goloso is the right place if you are craving for spongy and tasty cakes and you are somewhere in heart of Mumbai. Cake lovers check out this place and have some real fun!</item>
        <item>A mini South India on Dadar, Kamat Veg Fast Food is an awesome place to have some quick munchies like chole bhature, pani puri and your other favourite snacks.</item>
        <item>A good place to enjoy some Puneri Misal in Mumbai, The Kharvas you get here is also worth tasting. The dining area of this restaurant is very small, but the menu card is big.</item>
        <item>Delicious dabeli at Dadar, this is the place. Bhanushali Dabeli serves lip-smacking dabeli which have something unique in it, unlike other dabelis in the city!</item>
        <item>All that you can find in a Marathi House you get it here. Its very very authentic Maharashtrian restaurant good for some quick Maharashtrian style snacks in Dadar.</item>
        <item>A unique bhel with some unique flavour is what you get at Brij Albela in Wadala. The bhel is topped with chana, corn, cheese, mouth-watering kachha mango and what not!</item>
        <item>This place serves variety of chat items from pani puri to dahi puri. They give you all this while being light on your pocket and taking care of some hygiene too!</item>
        <item>If you have very less money in your pocket and still want to have some food which will help you give loud burp, Ramesh Da Dhaba is where you should head to.</item>
        <item>A small and cozy cafe, hangout spot for college students Bogeto Cafe in Matunga offers chatpata chat and other varieties of fast food. Light on your wallet too!</item>
        <item>If you want to taste epic sev puri cheese toast, head to this place you won\'t regret. Gupta Chat Center is very popular in Matunga for their good quality and superb taste.</item>
        <item>Rahul\'s Food Court is quite amazing place if you want to have some authentic street food in Matunga. They are known for their signature rolls and lip-smacking pasta.</item>
        <item>One of the oldest sandwich stalls in Matunga, Madhu Sandwich serving quality and tasty sandwiches probably since last 30 years is where you should head to if you are in Matunga</item>
        <item>A popular juice center in King\s Circle is known for it\'s delicious pav bhaji. Also it is quite popular for cool milkshakes, hot pizzas and grilled sandwiches.</item>
        <item>You won\'t find good seating arrangement, no quick service, and many other issues. But the fact is you will go back at this place again if you taste their grilled sandwich once.</item>
        <item>You will start hating traditional idli, if you taste different varieties of idlis at this place. The idli chutney fans get ready and head to this place quickly!</item>
        <item>Good quality, better service and best taste, this is how it goes at the Dairy Don outlet in King\'s Circle. The milkshakes and ice creams you get here are superb.</item>
        <item>Kakori House will offer you a good range of good food which is little expensive, but given the service and quality of food they provide they deserve it. Kakori Kebab is must!</item>
        <item>If you want good quality pastries and cakes for a big party, don\'t do the mistake of not going at this place. You would love to see a good variety and range of cake flavours.</item>
        <item>One of the very old and popular mithai locations in Mahim, they offer a good range of quality sweets made with pure ghee. Aflatoon Halwa is what they are known for.</item>
        <item>You will love eating kulfis at this place. They offer sweet kulfis in matkas with variety of flavours. Apart from kulfis they also offer delicious faloodas.</item>
        <item>If you are in some whhere in Sion and you are craving for some sweets, Maya Sweets is where you should head to. They offer authentic Punjabi Sweets with best quality.</item>
        <item>A1 Samosa as their name says, they serve A grade samosas with a lots of different varieties. Not only samosas you get other munchies too with reasonable rates.</item>
        <item>Thirsty folks automatically stop at this place. B. M. Fresh Juice Center offers a good range of fresh juices and the faloodas. A cool place to chill and beat the heat.</item>
        <item>If you have a sweet tooth this is your stop, you might talk about jalebis you get at J. J. Jalebi but the rabdi you get here steals the show. jalebi stands second at this place. </item>
        <item>Sukh Sagar in Chembur offers you a range of faloodas but they have something unique in their faloodas and that is the thick malai. The malai in falooda makes this place special.</item>
        <item>Fresh Fast Food as their intresting name says you will agree with them. This place is heaven for the street food lovers, you get the same street side taste with great hygiene.</item>
        <item>The kebab and roll point of Chembur, Kamrun Food Corner is where you get lip-smacking rolls made with crispy roti and soft fillings. Th spices in your food are in best proportion.</item>
        <item>Don\'t judge a book by it\'s cover and a food stall by it\'s ambience. This quote is rightly applicable at The Filling Place. The food you get here is awesome.</item>
        <item>A small place located in Chembur, with not so good ambience but the food you get here will make you go mad. The kulcha, chole, parathas and what not! Superb place and superb taste.</item>
        <item>Sindh Pani Puri House serves good variety of chat in Sindhi style. Their pani puri and dahi puri carries a lot of hype with it and they deserve it. Chat lovers go for it!</item>
        <item>If you want to have some tasty food in good quantity to satisfy your hunger and you have less money in your wallet. There is no need to worry, Bhatt Vishranti Gruha is the location.</item>
        <item>If you are somewhere in Navi Mumbai and you want perfect evening time snacks, Ganesh Vada Pav is where you should head to. With hot vada and spicy chutney it seems just perfect.</item>
        <item>Trupti Dosa in Vashi is absolute delight for all the South Indian cuisine fans. You get a range of dosas like jini dosa, pavbhaji dosa, cheese dosa and what not.</item>
        <item>A South Indian restaurant in Vashi, Yummy Foods do exactly what their name reads. Yummy Dosas, yummy pastas, yummy pizzas, yummy everything! They offer a great variety.</item>
        <item>If you are craving for a good and tasty dosa and you are somewhere in Vashi, don\'t make a mistake of missing out this place. They offer over 100 variates of lip-smacking dosas.</item>
        <item>Not so hygienic, not so fast service still it\'s crowded and only reason is their taste. The taste, the flavour and a big menu card with lot of variety is what makes the difference.</item>
        <item>If you want lip-smacking food at great price then Chhaya Sagar Restaurant is right place to go. They offer vada pav, misal pav, dosa, samosa, juices and lots of other tasty food.</item>
        <item>If you are very concerned of hygiene and quality and also want the same street food taste, you should head to Dosa Plaza in Sanpada for lip-smaking dosa and pav bhaji.</item>
        <item>Food Stop make sure you take a stop here. They offer a good range of snacks consisting of momos, sandwiches, pizzas, shawarma, falooda and what not! You will love this place.</item>
        <item>A good place to grab some lip-smacking snacks on the go. The pizza they offer is what you will keep bringing you back to this place again and again. Good value for money too!</item>
        <item>In case you are in Vidya Vihar and need some mind-boggling and finger-licking meal, you should check out Kutchhi Deli. Gujrati and Rajastani cusine is at it\'s best here.</item>
        <item>Achija is fast food restaurant in Ghatkopar with some good ratings by the local folks. This place is known for tasty pav bhaji delight, tawa pulav, garlic bread and what not!</item>
        <item>Blossom The Fusion Point in Ghatkopar is where you get some awesome food, awesome service and awesome ambience. It\'s a right place to spend awesome quality time.</item>
        <item>If you are craving for mouth-watering fusion food delight somewhere in Ghatkopar, Pure Milk And Snack Center is right place to go. Dosa lovers can\'t afford to miss this place.</item>
        <item>Located very close Ghatkopar station, if you are hungry and want\'t to have some heavy food this is the place. They offer a good quality of South Indian and North Indian dishes.</item>
        <item>This place has no seating arrangement, no proper service but you get some lip-smacking dosa delight.You get other tasty food items too! The food here is rated 10 out of 10.</item>
        <item>Cheese fans stop here, because here the food you get is very cheesy. Go for cheese grilled sandwich it is loaded with your favourite veggies and huge amount of cheese, you will love it!</item>
        <item>The gola stop is khau galli, Pooja Malai Gola serves a good range of great golas while maintaining the hygiene standards. You will love having golas at this cool place!</item>
        <item>Pop Tate\'s a popular place in Vikroli is always crowded with local foodies. A good place to hangout with your friends. Enjoy good music, tasty food and excellent service.</item>
        <item>It\'s not just another restaurant in Kanjurmarg, it\'s one of the popular food joint. They serve South Indian, Nort Indian, Chinese and Continental cuisines as well.</item>
        <item>If you are looking for a quick breakfast while being light on your pocket, Bajran Hotel is where you should head to. Have some lip-smacking quality snacks.</item>
        <item>A popular name when we talk about enjoying a momo treat. Appetite Momos serve a good range of tasty fried and steamed momos, don\'t miss this place if you are momo lover.</item>
        <item>Kantilal Damodar Doodhwala is a preety good place when it comes to serving quality sweets. This place has a good ambience and service is also good. Sweet lovers paradise!</item>
        <item>Vegetarian foodies in Bhandup prefer visiting this food destination. They offer South Indian and Chinese cuisines at affordable rates. A pretty good place for family dining too!</item>
        <item>A quick bite place in Bhandup, Golden Vada Pav. They serve crispy and tasty snacks. You get decent vada pav at less rate, anyways go for their tasty kanda bhaji.</item>
        <item>A pretty decent restaurant near Bhandup station, good hygiene, good service and good food is what you get here. And the best thing is it is light on your pocket too!</item>
        <item>Kalidas Mandya Masala Vada Pav is popular in Mulund. They come up with something new and unique called as masala vada pav. It\'s very spicy and super yummy, check out now!</item>
        <item>Lakhan Dosa Center in Mulund is known for the range of fusion dosas they serve. It is of great quality and also the price is not a burden for your wallet. 10 out of 10 marks!</item>
        <item>A local ice cream parlour in Mulund, Prabhu Icecream Parlour serves a good range of icecream flavours and types. This place holds decent amount of croud and also known for sodas.</item>
        <item>If you are somewhere in Thane and craving for mouth-watering pav bhaji delight, you should be at Canon Pav Bhaji and Snacks. Best thing is they are open till midnight 3 AM.</item>
        <item>This bakery in Thane is where you get good quality baked food. They are popularly known for Burgers and Pizzas and best part is they bake their own breads!</item>
        <item>The Green Box offers you variety of fresh fruit juices, mocktails, sandwiches and other snack items. It is very small eatery but the food is amazing with amazing cost.</item>
        <item>Priti Sandwich and Juices is quite popular place in Thane when it comes to having sizzling sandwiches and fresh juices quickly. It is also popular for milkshakes and pastas.</item>
        <item>Raj Mata Vada Pav in Thane is popular place in Thane where people often stop to take a quick vada pav bite. Don\'t miss the unique yellow chutney which they serve with vadapav.</item>
        <item>If you are craving for the best desert in Thane after a heavy meal, don\'t think for a second and head to this amazing kulfi destination. They serve a good range of tasty kulfis.</item>
        <item>If you want quality street food and you don\'t worry of your wallet, Lashkara in Bandra is your destination. They serve chat, sweets and deserts taking care of quality and hygiene.</item>
        <item>Eat Around The Corner is where you will find great ambience, great service, great food. You will find indoor AC seating arrangement and open outdoor seating arrangement at this place.</item>
        <item>Flavoursome chat place in Khar, Shankar Bhel offers you a variety of chats with some tangy and spicy flavoured chutneys. Craving for a quaick chat somewhere in Khar this is the place. </item>
        <item>Sindful as their name reads they serve authentic Sindhi food. The atmosphere is good here, however the most popular thing here is bhee tikki, a tikki made from lotus stem.</item>
        <item>Arth in Khar is perfect place to have a good time with your family. It has a superb ambience, nice music and great service. They serve some unique and lip-smacking North Indian food.</item>
        <item>If you are somewhere near Santacruz station and craving for some hot and tasty food, check out the hot and tasty samosa at Radha Krishna. They offer a good variety of sweets too!</item>
        <item>Avarya in Santacruz West serves a good range of farsan, sweets and snacks. If you are craving for something crispy, crunchy, hot and spicy don\'t miss this place.</item>
        <item>Tiffany\'s Resto And Bar is where you should go if you are craving for a pav bhaji delight and you are somewhere in Santacruz East. The pav is literally soaked in butter!</item>
        <item>Cheezzila is where you get Italian style food while taking care of your wallet. This is the budget place to eat some tasty snacks on the go! Perfect party place in Santacruz.</item>
        <item>If you ask of Vada Pav in Vile Parle there are many options to go to, Babu Vada Pav is one of the options. They serve lip-smacking and spicy hot vada pav at very less price.</item>
        <item>The sandwich and shakes point in Vile Parle West, Ice And Rolls offer cool chocolaty shakes and lip-smacking sandwiches and fusion dosas. The price is reasonable, variety is huge.</item>
        <item>Ram Krishna Restaurant in Vile Parle is known for South Indian cuisine. Also the serve some North Indian dishes and fast foods. However pav bhaji here stands out of all.</item>
        <item>If you are in Andheri and craving badly for some sweet food, rush to Firdous Sweet Confectionary. They offer a good variety of quality sweets and bakery items.</item>
        <item>Looking for best cakes in Andheri, Dale\'s Eden is your destination. It\'s basically a cake shop which also serves delicious sweets and bakery items. You will love going here!</item>
        <item>In Andheri, pav bhaji test the best only at Nootan Pure Veg Restaurant. The quality, quantity and service is excellent and the taste of pav bhaji here is above all!</item>
        <item>One of the top notch and unique restaurant in Andheri. They serve a range of thalis from Maharashtrian thali to Continental thali, you get it here. Great ambience and great service!</item>
        <item>If you want to have a quality icecream delight in Jogeshwari, you can\'t miss this place. Snow Bite icecream outlet offers a range of natural ice cream flavours with great quality.</item>
        <item>Don\'t go on it\'s name, Juhu Sealand doesn\'t offer sea food. They bring the Juhu food right in Jogeshwari, from faloodas to golas and icecreams. This place is the right place to chill.</item>
        <item>Badelal Chana And Chat Shop in Jogeshwari is perfect place to have evening snacks on the go. They offer a variety of options while maintaining a good quality and being cheap too! </item>
        <item>If you want refreshing juice somewhere in Jogeshwari, this the right juice spot for you. Central Juice Center offers some quality fresh juices and other snack varieties too!</item>
        <item>The sandwich king of Goregaon, Vasu\'s Laxmi Balaji Snacks is where you get something unique. The sandwiches and pizzas you get here are superb and you get them only here!</item>
        <item>If you are craving for Maharashtrian food in Goregaon you should be at Mai Veg. It\'s simple and homely restaurant, a right place to grab some lip-smacking maharashtrian delight.</item>
        <item>Shraddha Saburi Hotel in Goregaon is known for mouth-watering pav bhaji. They have very quick and fast while serving you, a right place for a quick pav bhaji bite on the go!</item>
        <item>Jain Sweet And Farsan House in Goregaon is right place to grab a hot and tasty samosa pav on the go. This is quite old sweet mart, checkout some sweets too, if you like them!</item>
        <item>If you want to have some cool flavoured sodas in Borivali, Jai Shree Radhe is your destination. Beat the heat with fresh and refrehing flavoured sodas in Borivali.</item>
        <item>A street side dosa stall in Malad, R. P. Dosa Center serves a range of lip-smacking dosas. The place is not that hygienic but the taste of dosas here is mind-blowing.</item>
        <item>Pani puri and chat lovers in Malad note down your destination, it\'s Rashmin Mithai Shop. They offer superp pani puri, also they offer a good range of mind-boggling sweets.</item>
        <item>A fast food and snacks joint in Malad, Surbi offers quality vada pav, lassi and other variety of snacks. It\'s a right place for evening snacks which takes care of wallet too!</item>
        <item>If you are somewhere in Borivali and you have never tasted a soya malai chaap, this is the right time and right place to do it. Just head to Healthy Bites quickly.</item>
        <item>Cheese lovers in Borivali should not miss this place. They serve lip-smacking dishes topped with extra cheese. Garlic bread topped with huge amount of cheese is a must try!</item>
        <item>Nirvana in Kandivali is an authentic Punjabi restaurant. They serve lip-smacking punjabi delights with great quality and great service. Spiciness lovers should definitely go here!</item>
        <item>Yoko Sizzlers in Kandivali is the right place to dine-out with your family. They serve variety of Indian Sizzlers. The ambience is great, service is quick and food is amazing!</item>
        <item>Founded in 1904, Kyani is considered to be the oldest still remaining Irani café in town. It\'s the old world charm that Kayani has managed to preserve from old Bombay.</item>
        <item>Located in Mumbai\'s famous art district Kala Ghoda, this cafe is also a gallery which showcases artwork, so enjoy your coffee with some beautiful art around you.</item>
        <item>As the name says \'Pizza By The Bay\', enjoy some delicious pizzas sitting right at Marine Drive. They offer the most amazing wood-fired gourmet pizzas.</item>
        <item>One of the finest dining located in Shivaji Park, best place to hangout with your family and friends while enjoying superb authentic Italian cuisine on offer.</item>
        <item>If you want some change and variety in food this is the place. This popular frankie location of Mumbai offers great variety of fantastic frankies in the city.</item>
        <item>From \'Swastika\' to \'Sandwizzaa\' the journey of this popular sandwich outlet is just amazing. The sizzling sandwiches you get here has unbeatable taste.</item>
        <item>Cafe Zoe is a restaurant-cafe which has won many food-awards, the food you get here is likely to make hole in your pocket but every penny is worth the bite you take.</item>
        <item>You can\'t call it just a hut when it is located in south Bombay, it is an heavenly place for momo lovers around the world. Enjoy the beautiful view of sea while you eat.</item>
        <item>The China of Mumbai, serves world class chinese food in the city. Manchurian lovers should check out this place atleast once, and satisfy their greedy soul.</item>
        <item>The name that will spontaneously come to your mind is \'Raju Chinese\', if you taste chinese bhel at his outlet. A goto location for a quick chinese gobble!</item>
        <item>Heaven for noodle lovers, Wok express serves wonderful wok noodles in the city. They have 16 outlets across the city, so you don\'t need to go too far!</item>
        <item>This restaurant might make hole in your pocket but the ambience, the food is just wow! A perfect location to spend some quality time with your friends and family.</item>
        <item>Known for mouth watering European and Italian cuisines, Smoke House Deli is a popular cafe with multiple outlets across the city. The soup they offer is worth tasting.</item>
        <item>One of the highly rated pav bhaajis in the city, if you plan to get here, make sure you don\'t judge this place by it\'s look because here food is at center stage not the decor!</item>
        <item>Mamledar Misal is heavenly place for the misal lovers across the city. You get mindblowing misal at this place at affordable rates with level of spiciness you love.</item>
        <item>A simple and homely place for all the Maharashtrian food lovers, Prakash has maintained it\'s quality and taste over last few decades. Prakash\'s Sabudana Wada is amazing.</item>
        <item>With a wide-range of parathas on offer, Only Parathas is the right place to check out some quality parathas in the city. The best part is parathas you get are made with desi ghee.</item>
        <item>The authentic Punjabi Dhaba in the city, Chawla\'s Dhaba is the perfect location to get into a complete Punjabi mood and taste lip smacking chole bhature in Mumbai.</item>
        <item>Khichdi lovers in the city can explore a range of yummy khichdi at Khichdi Samrat. They offer more than 10 types of khichdis with perfect blend of taste and quality.</item>
        <item>Mi Marathi is authentic restaurant to get into a Marathi Mood and Marathi Food. However the best part is menu card is in Marathi and waiter will speak in Marathi!</item>
        <item>Established in 2007, Girgaon Katta, one of the authentic Marathi restaurants of Mumbai serves lip smaking Marathi food with pride being light on your pocket.</item>
        <item>A certified location to taste the iconic food of Mumbai \'The Vadapav\'. Standing strong since last 35 years, Ashok Vada Pav is best in providing city\'s favourite snack.</item>
        <item>Very few people in the city are unaware of this popular place in Sion, The Guru Kripa offers hot and crispy samosas in Mumbai, you will be a fan of this place soon.</item>
        <item>Raj Kachori at Tewari Bros. is worth tasting. They are very consistent in serving the same taste and same quality since last decades. The Kachori is next to perfect!</item>
        <item>Kapil Dabeli Center is the location you need to check if you are Dabeli Dance lover. Check out the amazing dance moves of Kapil while makes a tasty Dabeli for you.</item>
        <item>At Food Spot, the classic dhokla recipe is presented in variety of ways. So dhokla lovers what you are waiting for get in your shoes and head to this place right now!</item>
        <item>The Irani-Parsi restaurant bar, Soda Bottle Openerwala has limited menu but unlimited fun. Perfect place to spend a great time with your siblings and friends.</item>
        <item>Elco, highly rated chat location of Mumbai visited by bollywood celebrities in the city. A perfect place to enjoy lip smacking pani puri with proper hygiene and quality.</item>
        <item>The two popular brothers Ram and Sham in Santacruz serve world class chat at a small cart. Often visited by celebrities too, they satisfy your chat hunger with proper hygiene.</item>
        <item>This place may not follow proper hygiene standards, quite heavy for your pocket too. But the tasty Dahi Puri they offer will make you ignore every other thing.</item>
        <item>Sharma Chat Bhandar, the Ragda Pattice place of Mumbai. It is a small place with super affordable prices. They serve one of the best Ragda Pattice of Mumbai.</item>
        <item>Don\'t get surprised to see a bright blue small cart surrounded by a huge crowd. It is Ashok Panipuri Wala, offering one of the tasty dahivadas in Mumbai.</item>
        <item>If you are SVKM student, you are well aware of this place. A goldmine for all the dosa lovers in the city. They offer a range of tasty dosas enough to get a loud burp.</item>
        <item>The South India of Mumbai, Banana Leaf offers variety of lip smacking South Indian dishes. The range of idlis they offer will keep you wanting for more and more.</item>
        <item>You don\'t need to go to Chennai to taste some lip smacking South Indian food. Cafe Madras, stands out when it comes to eating some authentic South Indian dishes.</item>
        <item>One of the few places in the city which offer Gujarati, Rajasthani and Maharshtrian food all under one roof. The puran poli you get here is very tasty!</item>
        <item>Modakam has a 45 year old history of serving up this sensational sweet Modak. If you are visiting Siddhivinayak Temple don\'t forget to check out this place.</item>
        <item>One of the authentic North Indian restaurant of Mumbai, Dilli Da Hatti offers one of the tastiest gajar halwas in the city. You will be back at this place again!</item>
        <item>From fresh farsan and namkeen to a variety of sweets, this little place is the right stop for sweet lovers. The jalebi they offer has unbeatable taste.</item>
        <item>The Bengali sweet item rasgulla is at its best at The Bombay Canteen. You will love this new version of Rasgulla that is Coffee Rasgulla served with salted caremel icecream.</item>
        <item>Heaven for gulab jamun lovers, sweetest sweet outlet of Mumbai, Jhama Sweets is were you get the top class Gulab Jamun. Even celebrities stop their cars at this outlet.</item>
        <item>Icekraft lets you customize your own icecream, your icecream is ready in front of you within 5 minutes. Check out the concept of ice cream in form of cigar rolls.</item>
        <item>Parsi Dairy Farm offers wide variety of Kulfis, which are sweet soft and milky. Established around 1917, this place also offers other high quality dairy items.</item>
        <item>The popular Falooda place of Mumbai, you will find very few people who are unaware of this iconic falooda location. They offer tremendous varieties of faloodas.</item>
        <item>VIG Refreshments, a dhaba style Punjabi food location offers lip smacking lassi in the city. This location is difficult to find but its popularity will get you there.</item>
        <item>Founded by two engineers, it is a perfect location to hangout with your family and friends and the best part here is "Meri Vali Chai".</item>
        <item>Iconic cafe of Mumbai, Prithvi Cafe is a perfect place to hangout with family and friends. Enjoy a cup of coffee in lush green outdoor seating arrangement.</item>
        <item>Established recently in 2015, Pizzeria offers authentic wood fire pizzas with rustic flavour in full display. Pizaa lovers get ready to attack!</item>
        <item>Powai has so many restaurants, but this place stands out when it comes to exploring some delicious pastas. One of the few Italian stand-alone restaurants in the city.</item>
        <item>A paradise for frankie lovers, Breadkraft will never disappoint all the vegetarians in the city. They have lots of delicious vegetarian frankies in their menu card.</item>
        <item>The Right Place is the right place to enjoy mouth watering and sizzling sandwiches. Their iconic chilli-coriander chutney makes this sandwich more special.</item>
        <item>The crunchy burger at Hard Rock Cafe melts in your mouth as you take a bite. You will hardly find a cheesy, creamy and crispy burger like this anywhere else in the city.</item>
        <item>You might have passed by this momos stall on Carter\'s. But you might not be knowing, this is the sacred stop in the city to enjoy the delight of mouth-watering momos.</item>
        <item>Another popular destination to eat authentic chinese dishes, they have multiple outlets in the city. Their Manchurian paired with fried rice has unmatched taste.</item>
        <item>At Wok In The Box, you can customize your own noodles by selecting the ingredients. They serve you noodles in a box so you can easily carry your noodles and enjoy them.</item>
        <item>Mantra in Powai serves you Punjabi and Chinese cuisines in a great ambience. The first thing you should do here when you enter is ask for a soup.</item>
        <item>From pav bhaji breakfast to pav bhaji dinner, this pav bhaji palace is always crowded. The best part about this place is how the women handle the show even in peak hours.</item>
        <item>Being in this business for more then 30 years, Aaswad serves mouth-watering Mahrashtrian and South Indian cuisines at the most affordable rates. Checkout their spicy misal. </item>
        <item>Their name speaks for what they serve, if you are craving for yummy and tummy filling parathas this is the place.Their parathas are huge and they serve it with dahi.</item>
        <item>The dal khichdi at Hitchiki is pure gold. Satisfy your tummy with this yummy meal exclusively at Hitchki. The khiched is prepared with oodles of ghee and served with pickle.</item>
        <item>Established in 1944, Tambe Arogya Bhuvan gives you a homely feel in every bite you take here.It serves mouth watering zunka bhakar with lots of other food stuffs.</item>
        <item>Established around 70 years ago, Aram is probably the oldest and most iconic place in CST. They serve spicy hot vada pav with special garlic chutney, you can\'t miss.</item>
        <item>The bustling store in Vile Parle, is known for its spicy and overloaded kachori. It has something special in it which drives people back to this place again and again.</item>
        <item>A popular dabeli joint in Charni Road, Little Bite Dabeli. It won\'t take time for you to locate this place as it is always crowded. They offer a wide range of dabelis.</item>
        <item>This outlet serves light and juicy dhokla, you won\'t find anywhere else in the town this easy. There is high probability of you being addicted to dhokla if you taste it here.</item>
        <item>The Parleshwar Vada Pav Samrat, is quick food stop especially for the college students. This is the right location to grab a quick bhajji pav if you are some where in Vile Parle.</item>
        <item>A bustling outlet in central suburbs is the right place to enjoy mouth-watering pani puri. The shop is loaded with lot of other tasty chat options but pani puri here stands out!</item>
        <item>Going strong since 1960, this place is known for \'Golden Bhel\', so called because the dish is sluiced with yellow split peas and turmeric. It has unmatched taste.</item>
        <item>If you are ready to stand and wait in long queue, Swati is the place you should head to. The offer some tasty dahi puri, each and every bite is worth the wait in long queue.</item>
        <item>Ganesh Chat Center is the right location to have some mouth-watering and tasty ragda pattice of all times. The place is quite small, so you should be early to get a seat.</item>
        <item>A colourfull and zesty version of dahivada is what you get at Monsoon, this iconic location is known for other chat items as well but the dahi vada here stands out!</item>
        <item>One of the oldest South Indian eateries of Mumbai, Hotel Ram Ashraya is the place you should head to if you are craving to have some authentic dosas in the city.</item>
        <item>Dakshinayan, a South Indian restaurant in Juhu serves authentic South Indian dishes in you plate. With unbeatable food, this restaurant is light on your pocket too!</item>
        <item>This 59 year old eatery, has some serious connection with modaks. Their dry fruit and fruit flavoured modaks are in demand through out the year. Sweet lovers be alert!</item>
        <item>A small joint located at the heart of Mumbai, Pancharatna Jalebi House offer tastiest jalebis along with crispy and tasty fafdas. Jalebi fans gather in long queues at this place.</item>
        <item>Sweet Bengal brings all the Bengali delights in this city. From rasgullas to mishti doi, this place serves authentic Bengali sweets. Right place to eat mouth-watering rasgulla.</item>
        <item>Fresh gulab jamun point of Mumbai, Karan Gulab Jamun serves soft and juicy gulab jamuns. They even offer variety of other sweets but the taste of gulab jamun is unmatched.</item>
        <item>Papa Cream serves ice creams made with liquid nitrogen right in front of you. They bring in some unique ice cream flavours too, so ice cream fans head to this place quickly!</item>
        <item>One of the oldest ice cream outlets in the city, New Kulfi Center brings for you a range of kulfi flavours. Grab your kulfi and head to the beach front which is nearby.</item>
        <item>Started way back in 1930, this place is a popular hangout spot in night. They offer chilled milkshakes, faloodas and icecreams while being light on your pocket. So, why waiting? </item>
        <item>One of the oldest sweet shops in Dadar, Kailash Mandir Lassi And Sweets offers thick and creamy lassi that too in 8 different flavours. The taste of this lassi is unmatched.</item>
        <item>A Brun Pav with extra butter and a cup of chai at Qutuz Irani Tea just before sunrise…Bliss!! Right place for a quick refreshment on the go.</item>
        <item>This quirky cafe is also a comic library. Leaping Windows is a quite interesting place to read comic books while having a refreshing and rejuvenating cup of coffee.</item>
        <item>Joey\'s Pizzas is the stop for pocket friendly and lip-smacking pizzas on the go. Loyal pizza fans can be seen standing outside this outlet waiting for their turn.</item>
        <item>Alfredo\'s, a Goan themed restaurant in the all time buzzing city is where you need to get some fresh air and fresh mood with amazing pastas on offer this place is real heaven.</item>
        <item>If you want to have a frankie feast you can\'t miss this place. They offer mouth watering and fantastic frankies at pocket friendly and very affordable rates.</item>
        <item>This place is heaven for sandwich lovers. Lucky Sandwich in Vile Parle has a big menu card with small rates when it comes to sandwiches. Load yourself with real sandwich stock!</item>
        <item>This Irish pub in Mumbai serves some best burgers in the city. Right place to visit with your colleagues after a stressful work at the office. Grab a burger and have some fun.</item>
        <item>One of the oldest momo stops in the city, Sernyaa is a place everyone should visit atleast once. The momos they serve have great variety and mind blowing taste.</item>
        <item>A small eating joint in the Andheri, Narayan Snack Parlour is the place to enjoy lip smacking chinese bhel with a dash of lemon on it. The goto chinese location of Mumbai.</item>
        <item>Wok This Way offers a wide range of noodles. The \'Only Veg Noodles\' location also allows you to customize your noodles. Put on your shoes and head to this place quickly!</item>
        <item>Authentic Chinese Restaurant, Firebowl has some mind-blowing and mouth-watering chinese food on offer. They have a very good variety of rice with less burden on your pocket.</item>
        <item>Pronto, a small and simple location which offers some chinese delights at most affordable rates. Pronto lives upto it\'s name and serves and delivers food quickly!</item>
        <item>Surrounded by number of other pav bhaji outlets, Shree Siddhivinayak Fast Food is what you should look for if you are at the beach. Finger licking pav bhaji - Tick!</item>
        <item>Established around 70 years ago, Aram is probably the oldest and most iconic place in CST. They serve hot and mouth-watering misal, you won\'t find this taste anywhere else.</item>
        <item>One of the best places if you love Maharshtrian Food. They offer authentic Marathi dishes at some pocket friendly rates. Sabudana vada is what you should go for, if you are here.</item>
        <item>A small eatery in Sion, is heaven for chole-bhature lovers in the city. The most important thing you need to taste this food is some patience, get ready to stand in long queue.</item>
        <item>Dal khichdi fans pick up your spoons and get ready. Spice Klup is a combination of innovation and authentic North Indian cuisines. The dal khichdi they offer has unmatched taste.</item>
        <item>Mithibai students have some interesting memories with this place. You will find more students here than in the classrooms, such is the hype of Anand Vada Pav Stall.</item>
        <item>The Punjab Sweet House, authentic Punjabi restaurant going good since many decades turns out to be a good place to check out with your family and enjoy some best samosas.</item>
        <item>Jain Sweet And Bhelpuri House is the location you need to go to consume a heavily loaded mouth-watering delicious snack - raj kachori. This kachori they serve is real gold!</item>
        <item>Dabeli lovers head to Matunga Dabeli to enjoy the dabeli delight. They load the hot pav with cheese slice and a perfectly cooked filling which will make you want more.</item>
        <item>Saurashtra Farsan Mart will offer you the dhokla delight. They serve soft and fluffy dhokla with lip-smacking green chutney. This place is few minutes away from Dadar station.</item>
        <item>A perfect place to hangout with a group of friends, play some board games, get a cup of tea with hot-tasty pakodas and have a great time. The iconic place to chill in Mumbai!</item>
        <item>Sharma Bhelpuri House, the all time bhelpuri location of Mumbai. They serve some seriously tasty bhelpuri. The sweet and sour chutneys spooned over it bring all the flavour!</item>
        <item>Close to Matunga station, Gupta Chat is where you get healthy plus tasty chat variates. They even take care of your pocket while serving with the best quality and hygiene possible.</item>
        <item>Kunj Vihar, best place to munch on healthy chat with some interesting taste. In the sev puri they offer here you will find sprouts instead of ragda, making it more tasty and healthy.</item>
        <item>Bikanervala at Vashi will offer you some serious snack options from North India. They offer packed snack varieties too, but the most interesting thing you get here is Dahi Vada.</item>
        <item>Narayan\'s Dosa brings in a vast range of regular and mouth-watering fusion dosas. The more you eat here the more you want, the tasty dosas will bring you back to this place again.</item>
        <item>Matunga has many South Indian outlets, but each of them have signature recipes. Here at Sharada Bhavan the upma you get has unbeatable taste, authentic upma made at its best.</item>
        <item>Vinay Health Home, it seems like a chemist outlet but it is not. This place takes utmost care of hygiene and your health while serving some delicious authentic Maharashtrian food.</item>
        <item>The Sigree Global Grill might call themselves as one of the best Greek and Lebanese restaurant in Mumbai, they have mastered a North Indian dish - The Gajar Halwa</item>
        <item>Located in heart of the city, Tip Top Farsan tops the list when it comes to serving some high quality farsan in the city. The jalebi the serve is unbeatable in taste. </item>
        <item>Sandesh Bengali Sweets is one of the first few outlets which introduced Mumbaikars to Bengali sweets. This place offers some tasty bengali sweets, try their rasgulla!</item>
        <item>Honey Gulab Jamun, as the name says this outlet makes gulab jamun as sweet as honey. In this outlet you will also find some great variety of namkeens too.</item>
        <item>One of the highly rated old Irani ice cream joints in South Bombay. K. Rustom offers handmade ice creams with some delicious ice creams at pocket friendly rates.</item>
        <item>Shahi Durbar serves a good range of pastas sandwiches and other snacks. But what stands out from all this is their creative kulfis which you get is 4 different forms.</item>
        <item>The legendray falooda place, Badshah falooda is serving some signature faloodas since 1900s, before all of us were born! Head to this place and enjoy the legendary taste.</item>
        <item>This place started to be a small food stall turned in to a buzzing restaurant in the city. A big glass of tasty lassi topped with thick malai is their speciality.</item>
        <item>Classical music, classical vibes and a cup of tea, a perfect start of a day. One of the best places to explore over 40 tea varieties in the city.</item>
        <item>Blue Tokai, one of the new successful coffee outlets of Mumbai serves you freshly brewed coffee with delectable baked cookies and other treats.</item>
        <item>Gustoso, Italian style restaurant in Mumbai offers authentic Italian treat. This place have some great ratings for the pizza the offer with some lively musical ambience.</item>
        <item>Little Italy, as their name says they prove it with some authentic pastas on offer. The have a big menu card which includes Italian, Lebanese and Mexican cuisines.</item>
        <item>If you are hungry for a frankie, mark this place in your mind. Roti N provides spicy and yummy frankie in some serious quantity which might make you burp loudly! </item>
        <item>Students of Nationals and MMK have more than 75% attendance at this place. Jay Sandwich stall offers lip-smacking sandwiches at pocket friendly rates.</item>
        <item>Woodside Inn serves some best burgers in the city. Enjoy a tasty and heavy burger accompanied by lively music and interesting fact is - it is open til 2 AM.</item>
        <item>Appetite Momos at Thane is where you get a wide range of momos. Their menu card is a-z of momos. From Vegetarian Momos to Paneer Achari Momos they have it all!</item>
        <item>This place is light on pocket when compared with the quality of food they serve. Peco Peco is where you will start visiting occasionally if you visit once.</item>
        <item>Fat Five Monks brings to you the finest of South East Asian cuisines. You can have some best noodles in the city at this place along with wide variety of salads and juices.</item>
        <item>If you are a fan of authentic chinese cuisine, Mainland China is your destination. They serve high quality chinese food in fabulous atmosphere around.</item>
        <item>Chilli and Onion restaurant is the right location if you worry about you pocket. They offer some authentic Asian cuisine at affordable rates. Do try their soup.</item>
        <item>Amar Juice Center, what\'s in a name? This place happens to be one of the most popular pav bhaji outlets of Mumbai. Here you get your favorite pav bhaji within few minutes!</item>
        <item>Hygiene and cleanliness is primary goal at Gokhale Upahar Griha. They have open to view kitchen to show the hygiene they maintain and the quality food they serve.</item>
        <item>Paratha lovers if you need some change and variety in your favourite food this is your place. Khasiyat serves lip smacking wide variety of parathas at affordable rates.</item>
        <item>Don\'t make a mistake of judging the place on its looks and decor, Shree Chole Bhature serves some real gold when you talk about food at this place. Don\'t judge a book by cover!</item>
        <item>Serving typical North Indian and Punjabi food, Pratap Da Dhaba is where you should rush to if your soul is craving for some authentic dal khichdi with achar and papad.</item>
        <item>Kutumbsakhi is common man\'s eatery founded by a NGO to support married house wives to earn some income. The pohe they serve has some genuine and homely taste.</item>
        <item>This 20 year old family run business, Graduate Vada Pav is one of the iconic vada pav location of Mumbai. Enjoy a Graduate Vada Pav with wide varieties of chutneys they offer.</item>
        <item>Delhi Highway, you might feel you are somewhere in Delhi if you are in this restaurant. The raj kachori they serve has the \'Delhi Wali Feeling\'. Try it to believe it!</item>
        <item>To taste authentic Kutchi Dabeli you don\'t need to go to Gujrat when it is so close to you. The Dilkhush Dabeli in Vile Parle West serves delicious dabeli at pocket friendly rates.</item>
        <item>Is it possible to get 8 different varieties of dhokla at one place? Yes nothing is impossible when Rajubhai Dhoklawala is here. They have experimented and come up with some delights.</item>
        <item>D. Damodar Mithaiwala serves great quality Indian sweets made with pure ghee and some mouth-watering snacks. Check out some pakodas, the quality and taste is just perfect.</item>
        <item>Popular since 1875, Vithal Family Restaurant And Bar is where you should head to if you are craving for a tempting bhel. They serve other food items too but the bhel stands out.</item>
        <item>If you are vegetarian foodie you are definitely going to love this place with lot of vegetarian delights on offer. Kailash Parbat is very popular for some mouth-watering chats.</item>
        <item>Khau Gali in Ghatkopar has many food stalls from chinese to desi food. But it is incomplete without chat stalls. The dahi vada you get at this place is lip smacking.</item>
        <item>This popular South Indian eatery in Mumbai, is know for the authentic South Indian dishes they make. The milky upma they serve is one of the best upma you don\'t get anywhere else.</item>
        <item>Established 70 years ago, Adarsh Mithai Mandir is well known modak point of Mumbai. A wide array of mouth- watering modaks are up for display at this place, don\'t get confused!</item>
        <item>Gajar Ka Halwa is what you should look for if you are at The Indian Affair. They serve some authentic Mughalai cuisines along with mouth watering gajar ka halwa.</item>
        <item>Brijawsi Bengali Sweets has a long menu card and a long queue. They offer a wide range of bengali sweets which are superb in taste and best in quality. Sweet lovers note down!</item>
        <item>Another place to enjoy some seriously sweet and tasty gulab jamuns in the city, Champaji Gulab Jamun House  will give you mouth melting gulab jamuns made in desi ghee.</item>
        <item>Where\'s My Cone, well you might find it at this ice cream outlet in Mumbai. They serve wide range of ice cream flavours and they can deliver at your home too!</item>
        <item>Himalaya, no you don\'t need to go to Himalaya when we have it in Mumbai. It is a small vegetarian joint and they serve some genuinely tasty kulfis in this city.</item>
        <item>This midnight meal of Mumbaikars can be found at Shalimar Cool Point. Shalimar is where you get a blast of sweetness in your mouth with some tasty falooda flavours.</item>
        <item>A place basked with positivity and liveliness, Garde Manger Cafe is where you get a cup of energetic coffee. This place is quite popular in Mumbai for its homely ambience and coffee.</item>
        <item>Pizza Express is where you can build you own pizza from base to toppings. They offer some authentic and mouth-watering pizzas in the city, which you won\'t find anywhere else.</item>
        <item>Their menu card starts with Classic Macaroni and ends with Cheese to Grilled Veg Spaghetti. With a huge range of pastas on offer, best thing is you can also toss veggies of your choice.</item>
        <item>Ideal spot for a quick bite of divine and mouth-watering variety of frankies at the heart of the city. You won\'t see frankies in their menu card, as they call it Naan Roll here..</item>
        <item>This sweet and snack parlour in Powai is where you get iconic sandwich in the city. Specially known for grilled and toast sandwich, the cheese toppings on it turns it into gold.</item>
        <item>This place is known for it\'s creativity when it comes to burgers. They are very unique when we talk about burgers. You get some twist in the taste of burgers and burger names as well!</item>
        <item>Bhukka Sher as their name says, this is the right place to fill your empty stomach with a range of mouth-watering momos. One of the few places in the city who serve tandoori momos.</item>
        <item>Slurp and Burp outlet in Borivali is specialist in serving American Fast Food, but it is quite interesting to know that the chinese bhel you get here is unbeatable in taste.</item>
        <item>If you want to load your stomach with good amount of tasty food at affordable rates Dynasty is the right location to check out. It is a small place but the noodles will make you mad.</item>
        <item>Hakka Express brings you your favourite noodles at your doorstep. The best part about this eatery is they offer you wide range of noodles at extremely affordable prices.</item>
        <item>This place is one of the oldest bakeries in Bandra, a small eatery in some disguised location. But wait don\'t judge this place before you try some delectable snacks.</item>
        <item>South Mumbai folks are well aware of this gem, located in Shivaji Park Oven Fresh serves Mexican Italian cuisines at extremely pocket friendly rates.</item>
        <item>Shabri is a pretty good place to have tasty pav bhaji. Ambience is not that fancy but the pav bhaji they serve is class! The sitting is good and the food served is worth every penny.</item>
        <item>New Anand Bhuvan is one of the oldest Misal Joints located in South Mumbai. This place is quite popular for some genuine Marashtrian food. The Misal is super spicy!</item>
        <item>If you are tired of eating the same paratha, it is time to experience the same food with western style. Paratha Mantra is where you get fusion parathas. Check out this place for a change!</item>
        <item>If you are quite serious about your health and still want to eat something delicious, Tipsy Terrace is the right place for you. What is more healthy and tasty then a multigrain khichdi!</item>
        <item>B. Merwan is the only place where you get this kind of Samosa in the city. The samosa you get here is filled with mawa unlike the regular samosa you have.</item>
        <item>Early bird catches the worm! This phrase is quite applicable at Joshi\'s  Dabeli House, head to this place early as possible to get something before they are completely sold out.</item>
        <item>Gaurav Sweets and Namkeen is where you get some tasty Gujrati snacks at great price without compromising the hygiene. They are professional when it comes to making dhoklas.</item>
        <item>Sai Veg World, more than a typical udipi joint, apart from their simple South Indian food they also serve Punjabi and Chinese cuisine but the chat they offer stands out of all.</item>
        <item>A sev puri garnished with lush green coriander and crispy sev makes this special and worth going. Jalram Snacks is one of the best chats because of the uniqueness they bring in!</item>
        <item>They have build their position and standards when it comes to serving good quality food with good quantity. With great service and great ambience they offer great ragda pattice.</item>
        <item>Fusion dosas are common these days, but Nandu Dosa takes this concept to next level by serving Manchurian dosa, Khakra dosa  and what not. The dosa creativity place.</item>
        <item>Established in 1921, one of the legandary modak outlets in the city Panshikar serves a huge range of modak from fruity variations to dry fruit modaks, all best in taste.</item>
        <item>Taste of Punjab has a wide range of North Indian cuisines and pretty ambience. One thing you should fix in your mind is to have a gajar ka halwa every time you come here.</item>
        <item>Harilal Kashidas Bhajiwala, is one of legendary shops which is 8 decades old. Their name might say bhajiwala but they are popularly known for fresh jalebi and fafdas they serve.</item>
        <item>Established around 100 years ago, one of the oldest Bengali Sweet joints in Mumbai , Bhaishankar offers the best quality Bengali Sweets. Their flavoured rasgulla, hats off!.</item>
        <item>Known for their creamy lassi, M. M. Mithaiwala is a quite reputed brand serving quality sweets in the city. Their gulab jamuns are often underestimated, give some respect!</item>
        <item>Apsara Icecream serves premium hand churned icecream with wide range of fruity and dry-fruit flavours. They are known for the quality and taste since last 40 years.</item>
        <item>Gokul Icecream is a popular name. This place is quite interesting when it comes to decor and ambience. The ice creams they serve are made in traditional home-style manner.</item>
        <item>You can close your eyes and point your finger anywhere in their menu card, you won\'t be disappointed. Order anything, they make it the best. Be it juices, shakes or faloodas!</item>
        <item>At Oye Teri in Borivali you will find their menu card filled with a range of kulchas. But what you will love the most is their awesome classic lassi with a twist of pineapple.</item>


    </string-array>


</resources>