<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="nv_s_disc_one">

            <item>Popularly known as \'Biryani King Of Mumbai\', Jaffer Bhai\'s Delhi Darbar established in 1973 still stands tall when it comes to producing best biryani of Mumbai.</item>
            <item>Bombay Duck not being a duck but lizardfish, is one of the iconic things to eat in Mumbai. But wait, where to eat? Ofcourse at any outlet of Gomantak, as simple as that!</item>
            <item>Goila Butter Chicken-\'Ratio and Proportion at its best!\' Chicken to Gravy, Sweet to Spicy and Onion to Tomato. They are just perfect at their calculations. </item>
            <item>Good place to try crispy and tasty chicken lolipops in the city. It has superb ambience and seating area. All in all, it is fantastic place to catch up. </item>
            <item>If you love eating rolls and wraps, if you have some unconditional love with sea food, believe me or not this is your place. Ultimate place for fish lovers.</item>
            <item>Home Chef All Day Dining is cozy cafe in Dadar, they offer some good quality snacks and variety of cakes. Check out spicy and hot Chicken 65 here, you will love it!</item>
            <item>The owners of this chain are of Tibetan origin, so making delicious momos is their cup of tea. The restaurant is ery tiny but the taste of their food is unmatched.</item>
            <item>Hotel Malvan Samudra as their name says, if you are craving for authentic Malvani food delight you can\'t afford to remove this place from your list. Check out now!</item>
            <item>One of the popular food chains of Bandra since last 17 years is this place, known for delicious shawarma. Extensive range of shawarma will keep you wondering what to try.</item>
            <item>It is a real gem in the crowd of so many food joints around, if you are eager to eat a bhurji pav. Irani chai and a bhurji pav at this place will take you to heaven. </item>
            <item>One of Bandra\'s most popular Irani cafes, Good Luck offers some delicious omelettes in the city. A perfect place to take a break and get tasty breakfast on the go.</item>
            <item>At Hotel Sindhudurg you will get to taste some authentic Malvani dishes. Try Surmai Malvani curry, Surmai or King Fish is popular fish in Malvani Restaurants. </item>
            <item>If you are looking for homely ambience and authentic Malvani food, this restaurant is made for you. Chaitanya offers Malvani delight while taking care of your wallet.</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nv_s_disc_two">

            <item>If you want a biryani in best proportion of rice to meat to masala, you have left with this option. They offer multiple options and varieties of biryani, don\'t get confused.</item>
            <item>About 45 years ago, a guy borrowed some money from his friend and started this wonderful place. Many things might have changed but one thing is constant, the taste of bombil.</item>
            <item>They are the first to bring the concept of butter chicken in Mumbai, way back in 1942! An interesting ambience and decor with interesting food, the taste you won\'t forget.</item>
            <item>Apple chicken is their speciality. They turn an ordinary chicken lolipop into heaven, the taste you will remember for years and bring you back to this place again and again.</item>
            <item>Populated with food lovers, its difficult to find this place vacant. You are likely to get addicted to this place if you try their chicken roti and other food items once.</item>
            <item>BKC Dive is a great place to enjoy some non vegiterian quality food in BKC while enjoying superb Bollywood music. It has superb ambience and good service with quality food!</item>
            <item>You are not a true momo fan if you are yet to visit this place. This is the perfect location to explore variety of momos specially the chicken and egg varieties.</item>
            <item>You will find number of restaurants in Powai but when you talk about eating mouth-watering Malvani food you can\'t forget Soul Curry. Kombi Vade at it\'s best!</item>
            <item>As the name says, this place manufactures world-class Shawarmas in your city. Along with lip smaking shawarmas this place also has some indoor games and books to read.</item>
            <item>This place serves a variety of egg dishes. The cost is little higher but the food served here is worth it. This place is a paradise for egg lovers in the city.</item>
            <item>This old cafe is heaven for Parsi style food lovers. Wake up early, head to this amazing place and grab a cup of popular Irani tea along with an omelette. </item>
            <item>One of the most popular seafood outlets in the city, Gajalee stands for what it is today. The sea food they offer is outstanding. A complete package for the sea foodies.</item>
            <item>One of the most popular seafood outlets in the city, Gajalee stands for what it is today. The sea food they offer is outstanding. A complete package for the sea foodies.</item>





    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nv_s_disc_three">

            <item>A 79 year old restaurant which started with just 7 dishes on their menu, today it is one of the popular biryani hotspots in the city. Vegans might get something interesting too.</item>
            <item>Inspired by the Konkan coast of Maharashtara and located at the heart of Mumbai, this place is the perfect place to try some lip-smaking fish dishes specially the Bombil fry.</item>
            <item>Enjoy their creamy butter chicken with chur chur naan, and praise us later. Book a table in advance or prepare yourself to wait it out, such is the hype of this place. </item>
            <item>If you believe in rumours, then this are the guys who brought the concept of chicken lolipop in Mumbai. Respect them and taste this food at their place, you won\'t regret.</item>
            <item>This is a small stall with tasty rolls, popularly known for burnt garlic chicken roll. Kathi Kebab Roll is really a hidden jewel, add it to your bucket list!</item>
            <item>Kaitlyn\'s Beer Garden in Bandra is a pub and bar. It has a indoor garden decor and they play live music while you have some good quality taty and mind-boggling meal.</item>
            <item>You cant call it just a hut when it is located in south Bombay, it is an heavenly place for momo lovers around the world. Enjoy the beautiful view of sea while you eat.</item>
            <item>Malvan Tadka in Thane is where Malvani sea foodat it\'s best. They also offer North Indian and Chinese cuisine but the Malvani food stands out of all. Enjoy spicy seafood!</item>
            <item>Explore some amazing shawarmas and satisfy your greedy soul at this place. This place also serves various other Lebanese dishes and ensures there is no hole in your pocket!</item>
            <item>Relax and order a chai and a bhurji pav, this vintage 90 years old cafe will take you back into the retro era. Enjoy the vibes along with a tasty bhurji pav! </item>
            <item>If you want to explore something unique along with omelette, this is the place. They turn tasty omelette into a tasty plus healthy omelette, try Greek salad omelette.</item>
            <item>Another iconic seafood restaurant of Mumbai, which offers iconic seafood. The \'gassi\' at Apoorva is a nice balance of chilly and tanginess. Enjoy authentic seafood here!</item>
            <item>Mahesh Lunch Home serves authentic Manglorean cuisine in the city. The thick prawn curry, bombil fry, appam and dosa is what you should die for at this crazy food outlet.</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nv_s_disc_four">

            <item>Being in this \'Biryani Business\' for last 94 years, their Biryani turns out to be a winner as Eid feasts go. You will find a resahmi white masala base instead of the red one.</item>
            <item>Being populated by food enthusiasts daily and popular for its homely and cosy ambiance this is the place for you if you wish to taste red coconut chutney with crispy bombil. </item>
            <item>Your body might be somewhere in Mumbai but your heart might be in some dhaba of Punjab, such is the taste of butter chicken at Punjab Grills.</item>
            <item>A small place with a big menu card, place to explore variety of chicken dishes. It is a quick stop to satisfy your hungry soul with tasty chicken lolipop and other varieties.</item>
            <item>Tibbs is a popular name when it comes to frankies. They have vast variety, it is quite normal for you to get confused. Select any you won\'t regret for sure! </item>
            <item>3 Wise Monkeys in Khar is a pub and eatery with old world charm. It is a great place to enjoy karaoke and live music while having tasty and lip-smacking non vegetarian delights</item>
            <item>Here you will find an excellent collection of momos - veg, non-veg, fried, steamed. Check out their steamed chicken momos and don\'t forget to ask for extra red chutney!</item>
            <item>Amcho Koliwado offers traditional Malvani food. It\'s a small place with interesting decor and great service. The seafood and chicken dishes are at their best here!</item>
            <item>You don\'t need to be a King to be at King\'s Shawarma, a pocket friendly location to enjoy a big range of lip smacking shawarmas in your city.</item>
            <item>A small joint in Goregaon serving delicious bhurji pav since last 30 years. The egg bhurji you get here is simply lip smacking and the taste will bring you back again.</item>
            <item>Another Irani cafe you shoud check out to satisfy your greedy soul. They offer omellets, fried eggs, brun muska and special Irani chai. Worth visiting place!</item>
            <item>They don\'t keep you waiting for some delicious Malvani meal. Incredible service and some high quality tasty food is what they offer. So what you are thinking?</item>
            <item>Inspired by the Konkan coast of Maharashtara and located at the heart of Mumbai, this place is the perfect place to try some lip-smaking fish dishes specially the Bombil fry.</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nv_s_disc_five">

            <item>If you need something different than the traditional style biryani, this is the perfect place for you. Exclusively explore the concept of \'Chicken Tikka Biryani\'</item>
            <item>Offering an array of seafood varieties, this is one of the places to check out bombil fry. Crispy bombil fry and a glass of cool sol kadi, a perfect combination!</item>
            <item>Again, one of the oldest chains in the city to offer lip-smaking Butter chicken to staisfy your soul. Perfect place to hangout with family and friends.</item>
            <item>The best thing about chicken lolipop is you don\'t need to always go to a restaurant to taste this heaven, sometimes check out some bakeries too and get surprised!</item>
            <item>Right place to enjoy softest and most delicious mutton rolls in the city at unbelievable price. The other options and varieties will also make you go mad.</item>
            <item>Hoppumm in Bandra is a great place to dine-out with your family for a non-vegetarian food feast. If you want to taste Sri Lankan cuisine you should check-out here.</item>
            <item>Tandoori momos of Bhukkha Sher are getting more and more popular in the city. The quality and quantity of stuffing is just perfect and will definitely bring you back.</item>
            <item>Food N Flame is a very small place in Andheri, they serve lip-smacking sea food and North Indian dishes. The Kombi Vade you get here are mind-boggling, you will be back here!</item>
            <item>This juice center is not juice center, it is one of the popular shawarma destinations of Mumbai. Other tasty food items here will also give you a reason to visit this place again.</item>
            <item>Perfect location for a quick pocket friendly bhurji pav breakfast. The Irani style cafe is popular among the college students. Right place for a quick bhurji pav bite.</item>
            <item>Bagel shop is right location not just to taste some delicious bagel in the city but also omelette and egg dishes. It is a pet friendly place, so take them with you!</item>
            <item>This place is a hidden treasure in the city, a small place quite difficult to find. But as soon as you reach this place the food is worth the hard work you do to get here.</item>
            <item>A small place with quick service, Jai Hind Lunch Home is where you get best fish dishes you ever had. Sea food lovers cannot afford to miss this superb place in Bandra.</item>


    </string-array>

</resources>