<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="s_disc_one">
        <item>Founded in 1904, Kyani is considered to be the oldest still remaining Irani café in town. It\'s the old world charm that Kayani has managed to preserve from old Bombay.</item>
        <item>Located in Mumbai\'s famous art district Kala Ghoda, this cafe is also a gallery which showcases artwork, so enjoy your coffee with some beautiful art around you.</item>
        <item>As the name says \'Pizza By The Bay\', enjoy some delicious pizzas sitting right at Marine Drive. They offer the most amazing wood-fired gourmet pizzas.</item>
        <item>One of the finest dining located in Shivaji Park, best place to hangout with your family and friends while enjoying superb authentic Italian cuisine on offer.</item>
        <item>If you want some change and variety in food this is the place. This popular frankie location of Mumbai offers great variety of fantastic frankies in the city.</item>
        <item>From \'Swastika\' to \'Sandwizzaa\' the journey of this popular sandwich outlet is just amazing. The sizzling sandwiches you get here has unbeatable taste.</item>
        <item>Cafe Zoe is a restaurant-cafe which has won many food-awards, the food you get here is likely to make hole in your pocket but every penny is worth the bite you take.</item>
        <item>You can\'t call it just a hut when it is located in south Bombay, it is an heavenly place for momo lovers around the world. Enjoy the beautiful view of sea while you eat.</item>
        <item>The China of Mumbai, serves world class chinese food in the city. Manchurian lovers should check out this place atleast once, and satisfy their greedy soul.</item>
        <item>The name that will spontaneously come to your mind is \'Raju Chinese\', if you taste chinese bhel at his outlet. A goto location for a quick chinese gobble!</item>
        <item>Heaven for noodle lovers, Wok express serves wonderful wok noodles in the city. They have 16 outlets across the city, so you don\'t need to go too far!</item>
        <item>This restaurant might make hole in your pocket but the ambience, the food is just wow! A perfect location to spend some quality time with your friends and family.</item>
        <item>Known for mouth watering European and Italian cuisines, Smoke House Deli is a popular cafe with multiple outlets across the city. The soup they offer is worth tasting.</item>
        <item>One of the highly rated pav bhaajis in the city, if you plan to get here, make sure you don\'t judge this place by it\'s look because here food is at center stage not the decor!</item>
        <item>Mamledar Misal is heavenly place for the misal lovers across the city. You get mindblowing misal at this place at affordable rates with level of spiciness you love.</item>
        <item>A simple and homely place for all the Maharashtrian food lovers, Prakash has maintained it\'s quality and taste over last few decades. Prakash\'s Sabudana Wada is amazing.</item>
        <item>With a wide-range of parathas on offer, Only Parathas is the right place to check out some quality parathas in the city. The best part is parathas you get are made with desi ghee.</item>
        <item>The authentic Punjabi Dhaba in the city, Chawla\'s Dhaba is the perfect location to get into a complete Punjabi mood and taste lip smacking chole bhature in Mumbai.</item>
        <item>Khichdi lovers in the city can explore a range of yummy khichdi at Khichdi Samrat. They offer more than 10 types of khichdis with perfect blend of taste and quality.</item>
        <item>Mi Marathi is authentic restaurant to get into a Marathi Mood and Marathi Food. However the best part is menu card is in Marathi and waiter will speak in Marathi!</item>
        <item>Established in 2007, Girgaon Katta, one of the authentic Marathi restaurants of Mumbai serves lip smaking Marathi food with pride being light on your pocket.</item>
        <item>A certified location to taste the iconic food of Mumbai \'The Vadapav\'. Standing strong since last 35 years, Ashok Vada Pav is best in providing city\'s favourite snack.</item>
        <item>Very few people in the city are unaware of this popular place in Sion, The Guru Kripa offers hot and crispy samosas in Mumbai, you will be a fan of this place soon.</item>
        <item>Raj Kachori at Tewari Bros. is worth tasting. They are very consistent in serving the same taste and same quality since last decades. The Kachori is next to perfect!</item>
        <item>Kapil Dabeli Center is the location you need to check if you are Dabeli Dance lover. Check out the amazing dance moves of Kapil while makes a tasty Dabeli for you.</item>
        <item>At Food Spot, the classic dhokla recipe is presented in variety of ways. So dhokla lovers what you are waiting for get in your shoes and head to this place right now!</item>
        <item>The Irani-Parsi restaurant bar, Soda Bottle Openerwala has limited menu but unlimited fun. Perfect place to spend a great time with your siblings and friends.</item>
        <item>Elco, highly rated chat location of Mumbai visited by bollywood celebrities in the city. A perfect place to enjoy lip smacking pani puri with proper hygiene and quality.</item>
        <item>The two popular brothers Ram and Sham in Santacruz serve world class chat at a small cart. Often visited by celebrities too, they satisfy your chat hunger with proper hygiene.</item>
        <item>This place may not follow proper hygiene standards, quite heavy for your pocket too. But the tasty Dahi Puri they offer will make you ignore every other thing.</item>
        <item>The two popular brothers Ram and Sham in Santacruz serve world class chat at a small cart. Often visited by celebrities too, they satisfy your chat hunger with proper hygiene.</item>
        <item>Sharma Chat Bhandar, the Ragda Pattice place of Mumbai. It is a small place with super affordable prices. They serve one of the best Ragda Pattice of Mumbai.</item>
        <item>Don\'t get surprised to see a bright blue small cart surrounded by a huge crowd. It is Ashok Panipuri Wala, offering one of the tasty dahivadas in Mumbai.</item>
        <item>If you are SVKM student, you are well aware of this place. A goldmine for all the dosa lovers in the city. They offer a range of tasty dosas enough to get a loud burp.</item>
        <item>The South India of Mumbai, Banana Leaf offers variety of lip smacking South Indian dishes. The range of idlis they offer will keep you wanting for more and more.</item>
        <item>The South India of Mumbai, Banana Leaf offers variety of lip smacking South Indian dishes. The authentic medu vada they offer will take you to South India.</item>
        <item>You don\'t need to go to Chennai to taste some lip smacking South Indian food. Cafe Madras, stands out when it comes to eating some authentic South Indian dishes.</item>
        <item>The South India of Mumbai, Banana Leaf offers variety of lip smacking South Indian dishes. The authentic Uttapa they offer is simply amazing and worth tasting.</item>
        <item>One of the few places in the city which offer Gujarati, Rajasthani and Maharshtrian food all under one roof. The puran poli you get here is very tasty!</item>
        <item>Modakam has a 45 year old history of serving up this sensational sweet Modak. If you are visiting Siddhivinayak Temple don\'t forget to check out this place.</item>
        <item>One of the authentic North Indian restaurant of Mumbai, Dilli Da Hatti offers one of the tastiest gajar halwas in the city. You will be back at this place again!</item>
        <item>From fresh farsan and namkeen to a variety of sweets, this little place is the right stop for sweet lovers. The jalebi they offer has unbeatable taste.</item>
        <item>The Bengali sweet item rasgulla is at its best at The Bombay Canteen. You will love this new version of Rasgulla that is Coffee Rasgulla served with salted caremel icecream.</item>
        <item>Heaven for gulab jamun lovers, sweetest sweet outlet of Mumbai, Jhama Sweets is were you get the top class Gulab Jamun. Even celebrities stop their cars at this outlet.</item>
        <item>Icekraft lets you customize your own icecream, your icecream is ready in front of you within 5 minutes. Check out the concept of ice cream in form of cigar rolls.</item>
        <item>Parsi Dairy Farm offers wide variety of Kulfis, which are sweet soft and milky. Established around 1917, this place also offers other high quality dairy items.</item>
        <item>The popular Falooda place of Mumbai, you will find very few people who are unaware of this iconic falooda location. They offer tremendous varieties of faloodas.</item>
        <item>VIG Refreshments, a dhaba style Punjabi food location offers lip smacking lassi in the city. This location is difficult to find but its popularity will get you there.</item>




    </string-array>

    <string-array name="s_disc_two">

        <item>Founded by two engineers, it is a perfect location to hangout with your family and friends and the best part here is "Meri Vali Chai".</item>
        <item>Iconic cafe of Mumbai, Prithvi Cafe is a perfect place to hangout with family and friends. Enjoy a cup of coffee in lush green outdoor seating arrangement.</item>
        <item>Established recently in 2015, Pizzeria offers authentic wood fire pizzas with rustic flavour in full display. Pizaa lovers get ready to attack!</item>
        <item>Powai has so many restaurants, but this place stands out when it comes to exploring some delicious pastas. One of the few Italian stand-alone restaurants in the city.</item>
        <item>A paradise for frankie lovers, Breadkraft will never disappoint all the vegetarians in the city. They have lots of delicious vegetarian frankies in their menu card.</item>
        <item>The Right Place is the right place to enjoy mouth watering and sizzling sandwiches. Their iconic chilli-coriander chutney makes this sandwich more special.</item>
        <item>The crunchy burger at Hard Rock Cafe melts in your mouth as you take a bite. You will hardly find a cheesy, creamy and crispy burger like this anywhere else in the city.</item>
        <item>You might have passed by this momos stall on Carter\'s. But you might not be knowing, this is the sacred stop in the city to enjoy the delight of mouth-watering momos.</item>
        <item>Another popular destination to eat authentic chinese dishes, they have multiple outlets in the city. Their Manchurian paired with fried rice has unmatched taste.</item>
        <item>Elco, highly rated chat location of Mumbai visited by bollywood celebrities in the city. A perfect place to enjoy lip smacking chinese bhel with proper hygiene and quality.</item>
        <item>At Wok In The Box, you can customize your own noodles by selecting the ingredients. They serve you noodles in a box so you can easily carry your noodles and enjoy them.</item>
        <item>A value for money location, you get what you pay for. If you don\'t love chinese food this is the place you should check out, you will ask for more chinese at this place.</item>
        <item>Mantra in Powai serves you Punjabi and Chinese cuisines in a great ambience. The first thing you should do here when you enter is ask for a soup.</item>
        <item>From pav bhaji breakfast to pav bhaji dinner, this pav bhaji palace is always crowded. The best part about this place is how the women handle the show even in peak hours.</item>
        <item>Being in this business for more then 30 years, Aaswad serves mouth-watering Mahrashtrian and South Indian cuisines at the most affordable rates. Checkout their spicy misal. </item>
        <item>Being in this business for more then 30 years, Aaswad serves mouth-watering Mahrashtrian and South Indian cuisines at the most affordable rates. Checkout their sabudana vada.</item>
        <item>Their name speaks for what they serve, if you are craving for yummy and tummy filling parathas this is the place.Their parathas are huge and they serve it with dahi.</item>
        <item>Very few people in the city are unaware of this popular place in Sion, The Guru Kripa offers unmatched chole bhature in the city, you will be a fan of this place soon.</item>
        <item>The dal khichdi at Hitchiki is pure gold. Satisfy your tummy with this yummy meal exclusively at Hitchki. The khiched is prepared with oodles of ghee and served with pickle.</item>
        <item>A simple and homely place for all the Maharashtrian food lovers, Prakash has maintained it\'s quality and taste over last few decades. Prakash\'s pohe is just amazing.</item>
        <item>Established in 1944, Tambe Arogya Bhuvan gives you a homely feel in every bite you take here.It serves mouth watering zunka bhakar with lots of other food stuffs.</item>
        <item>Established around 70 years ago, Aram is probably the oldest and most iconic place in CST. They serve spicy hot vada pav with special garlic chutney, you can\'t miss.</item>
        <item>The Tewari Bros. bring you iconic Samosa in the city. They serve hot, crispy and aloo loaded Samosas along with spicy green chutney. Every bite will make you want more.</item>
        <item>The bustling store in Vile Parle, is known for its spicy and overloaded kachori. It has something special in it which drives people back to this place again and again.</item>
        <item>A popular dabeli joint in Charni Road, Little Bite Dabeli. It won\'t take time for you to locate this place as it is always crowded. They offer a wide range of dabelis.</item>
        <item>This outlet serves light and juicy dhokla, you won\'t find anywhere else in the town this easy. There is high probability of you being addicted to dhokla if you taste it here.</item>
        <item>The Parleshwar Vada Pav Samrat, is quick food stop especially for the college students. This is the right location to grab a quick bhajji pav if you are some where in Vile Parle.</item>
        <item>A bustling outlet in central suburbs is the right place to enjoy mouth-watering pani puri. The shop is loaded with lot of other tasty chat options but pani puri here stands out!</item>
        <item>Going strong since 1960, this place is known for \'Golden Bhel\', so called because the dish is sluiced with yellow split peas and turmeric. It has unmatched taste.</item>
        <item>If you are ready to stand and wait in long queue, Swati is the place you should head to. The offer some tasty dahi puri, each and every bite is worth the wait in long queue.</item>
        <item>If you are ready to stand and wait in long queue, Swati is the place you should head to. The offer some tasty sev puri, each and every bite is worth the wait in long queue.</item>
        <item>Ganesh Chat Center is the right location to have some mouth-watering and tasty ragda pattice of all times. The place is quite small, so you should be early to get a seat.</item>
        <item>A colourfull and zesty version of dahivada is what you get at Monsoon, this iconic location is known for other chat items as well but the dahi vada here stands out!</item>
        <item>One of the oldest South Indian eateries of Mumbai, Hotel Ram Ashraya is the place you should head to if you are craving to have some authentic dosas in the city.</item>
        <item>Dakshinayan, a South Indian restaurant in Juhu serves authentic South Indian dishes in you plate. With unbeatable food, this restaurant is light on your pocket too!</item>
        <item>One of the oldest South Indian eateries of Mumbai, Hotel Ram Ashraya is the place you should head to if you are craving to have some authentic medu vada in the city.</item>
        <item>One of the oldest South Indian eateries of Mumbai, Hotel Ram Ashraya is the place you should head to if you are craving to have some authentic upma in the city.</item>
        <item>One of the oldest South Indian eateries of Mumbai, Hotel Ram Ashraya is the place you should head to if you are craving to have some authentic utappa in the city.</item>
        <item>If you are ready to stand and wait in long queues, Swati is the place you should head to. The offer some tasty puran poli, each and every bite is worth the wait in long queue.</item>
        <item>This 59 year old eatery, has some serious connection with modaks. Their dry fruit and fruit flavoured modaks are in demand through out the year. Sweet lovers be alert!</item>
        <item>Very few people in the city are unaware of this popular place in Sion, The Guru Kripa offers mouth-watering gajar halwa in Mumbai, you will be a fan of this place soon.</item>
        <item>A small joint located at the heart of Mumbai, Pancharatna Jalebi House offer tastiest jalebis along with crispy and tasty fafdas. Jalebi fans gather in long queues at this place.</item>
        <item>Sweet Bengal brings all the Bengali delights in this city. From rasgullas to mishti doi, this place serves authentic Bengali sweets. Right place to eat mouth-watering rasgulla.</item>
        <item>Fresh gulab jamun point of Mumbai, Karan Gulab Jamun serves soft and juicy gulab jamuns. They even offer variety of other sweets but the taste of gulab jamun is unmatched.</item>
        <item>Papa Cream serves ice creams made with liquid nitrogen right in front of you. They bring in some unique ice cream flavours too, so ice cream fans head to this place quickly!</item>
        <item>One of the oldest ice cream outlets in the city, New Kulfi Center brings for you a range of kulfi flavours. Grab your kulfi and head to the beach front which is nearby.</item>
        <item>Started way back in 1930, this place is a popular hangout spot in night. They offer chilled milkshakes, faloodas and icecreams while being light on your pocket. So, why waiting? </item>
        <item>One of the oldest sweet shops in Dadar, Kailash Mandir Lassi And Sweets offers thick and creamy lassi that too in 8 different flavours. The taste of this lassi is unmatched.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="s_disc_three">

        <item>A Brun Pav with extra butter and a cup of chai at Qutuz Irani Tea just before sunrise…Bliss!! Right place for a quick refreshment on the go.</item>
        <item>This quirky cafe is also a comic library. Leaping Windows is a quite interesting place to read comic books while having a refreshing and rejuvenating cup of coffee.</item>
        <item>Joey\'s Pizzas is the stop for pocket friendly and lip-smacking pizzas on the go. Loyal pizza fans can be seen standing outside this outlet waiting for their turn.</item>
        <item>Alfredo\'s, a Goan themed restaurant in the all time buzzing city is where you need to get some fresh air and fresh mood with amazing pastas on offer this place is real heaven.</item>
        <item>If you want to have a frankie feast you can\'t miss this place. They offer mouth watering and fantastic frankies at pocket friendly and very affordable rates.</item>
        <item>This place is heaven for sandwich lovers. Lucky Sandwich in Vile Parle has a big menu card with small rates when it comes to sandwiches. Load yourself with real sandwich stock!</item>
        <item>This Irish pub in Mumbai serves some best burgers in the city. Right place to visit with your colleagues after a stressful work at the office. Grab a burger and have some fun.</item>
        <item>One of the oldest momo stops in the city, Sernyaa is a place everyone should visit atleast once. The momos they serve have great variety and mind blowing taste.</item>
        <item>The name that will spontaneously come to your mind is \'Raju Chinese\', if you taste chinese food at this outlet. A goto location for a quick chinese gobble!</item>
        <item>A small eating joint in the Andheri, Narayan Snack Parlour is the place to enjoy lip smacking chinese bhel with a dash of lemon on it. The goto chinese location of Mumbai.</item>
        <item>Wok This Way offers a wide range of noodles. The \'Only Veg Noodles\' location also allows you to customize your noodles. Put on your shoes and head to this place quickly!</item>
        <item>Authentic Chinese Restaurant, Firebowl has some mind-blowing and mouth-watering chinese food on offer. They have a very good variety of rice with less burden on your pocket.</item>
        <item>Pronto, a small and simple location which offers some chinese delights at most affordable rates. Pronto lives upto it\'s name and serves and delivers food quickly!</item>
        <item>Surrounded by number of other pav bhaji outlets, Shree Siddhivinayak Fast Food is what you should look for if you are at the beach. Finger licking pav bhaji - Tick!</item>
        <item>Established around 70 years ago, Aram is probably the oldest and most iconic place in CST. They serve hot and mouth-watering misal, you won\'t find this taste anywhere else.</item>
        <item>One of the best places if you love Maharshtrian Food. They offer authentic Marathi dishes at some pocket friendly rates. Sabudana vada is what you should go for, if you are here.</item>
        <item>Iconic cafe of Mumbai, Prithvi Cafe is a perfect place to hangout with family and friends. Enjoy some lip-smacking parathas in lush green outdoor seating arrangement.</item>
        <item>A small eatery in Sion, is heaven for chole-bhature lovers in the city. The most important thing you need to taste this food is some patience, get ready to stand in long queue.</item>
        <item>Dal khichdi fans pick up your spoons and get ready. Spice Klup is a combination of innovation and authentic North Indian cuisines. The dal khichdi they offer has unmatched taste.</item>
        <item>Aram Hotel in Fort is the right place to enjoy authentic Maharashtrian cuisines in the city. The mouth-watering pohe they offer is worth tasting. Don\'t wait, go for it!</item>
        <item>Aram Hotel in Fort is the right place to enjoy authentic Maharashtrian cuisines in the city. The mouth-watering zunka bhakar they offer is worth tasting. Don\'t wait, go for it!</item>
        <item>Mithibai students have some interesting memories with this place. You will find more students here than in the classrooms, such is the hype of Anand Vada Pav Stall.</item>
        <item>The Punjab Sweet House, authentic Punjabi restaurant going good since many decades turns out to be a good place to check out with your family and enjoy some best samosas.</item>
        <item>Jain Sweet And Bhelpuri House is the location you need to go to consume a heavily loaded mouth-watering delicious snack - raj kachori. This kachori they serve is real gold!</item>
        <item>Dabeli lovers head to Matunga Dabeli to enjoy the dabeli delight. They load the hot pav with cheese slice and a perfectly cooked filling which will make you want more.</item>
        <item>Saurashtra Farsan Mart will offer you the dhokla delight. They serve soft and fluffy dhokla with lip-smacking green chutney. This place is few minutes away from Dadar station.</item>
        <item>A perfect place to hangout with a group of friends, play some board games, get a cup of tea with hot-tasty pakodas and have a great time. The iconic place to chill in Mumbai!</item>
        <item>Very few people in the city are unaware of this popular place in Sion, The Guru Kripa offers lip-smacking pani puri in Mumbai, you will be a fan of this place soon.</item>
        <item>Sharma Bhelpuri House, the all time bhelpuri location of Mumbai. They serve some seriously tasty bhelpuri. The sweet and sour chutneys spooned over it bring all the flavour!</item>
        <item>Close to Matunga station, Gupta Chat is where you get healthy plus tasty chat variates. They even take care of your pocket while serving with the best quality and hygiene.</item>
        <item>Kunj Vihar, best place to munch on healthy chat with some interesting taste. In the sev puri they offer here you will find sprouts instead of ragda, making it more tasty.</item>
        <item>Very few people in the city are unaware of this popular place in Sion, The Guru Kripa offers lip-smacking ragda pattice in Mumbai, you will be a fan of this place soon.</item>
        <item>Bikanervala at Vashi will offer you some serious snack options from North India. They offer packed snack varieties too, but the most interesting thing you get here is Dahi Vada.</item>
        <item>Narayan\'s Dosa brings in a vast range of regular and mouth-watering fusion dosas. The more you eat here the more you want, the tasty dosas will bring you back to this place.</item>
        <item>You don\'t need to go to Chennai to taste some lip smacking South Indian food. Cafe Madras, stands out when it comes to eating some authentic South Indian dishes.</item>
        <item>You don\'t need to go to Chennai to taste some lip smacking South Indian food. Cafe Madras, stands out when it comes to eating some authentic South Indian dishes.</item>
        <item>Matunga has many South Indian outlets, but each of them have signature recipes. Here at Sharada Bhavan the upma you get has unbeatable taste, authentic upma made at its best.</item>
        <item>You don\'t need to go to Chennai to taste some lip smacking South Indian food. Cafe Madras, stands out when it comes to eating some authentic South Indian dishes.</item>
        <item>Vinay Health Home, it seems like a chemist outlet but it is not. This place takes utmost care of hygiene and your health while serving some delicious authentic food.</item>
        <item>Being in this business for more then 30 years, Aaswad serves mouth-watering Mahrashtrian and South Indian cuisines at the most affordable rates. Checkout their modaks. </item>
        <item>The Sigree Global Grill might call themselves as one of the best Greek and Lebanese restaurant in Mumbai, they have mastered a North Indian dish - The Gajar Halwa</item>
        <item>Located in heart of the city, Tip Top Farsan tops the list when it comes to serving some high quality farsan in the city. The jalebi the serve is unbeatable in taste. </item>
        <item>Sandesh Bengali Sweets is one of the first few outlets which introduced Mumbaikars to Bengali sweets. This place offers some tasty bengali sweets, try their rasgulla!</item>
        <item>Honey Gulab Jamun, as the name says this outlet makes gulab jamun as sweet as honey. In this outlet you will also find some great variety of namkeens too.</item>
        <item>One of the highly rated old Irani ice cream joints in South Bombay. K. Rustom offers handmade ice creams with some delicious ice creams at pocket friendly rates.</item>
        <item>Shahi Durbar serves a good range of pastas sandwiches and other snacks. But what stands out from all this is their creative kulfis which you get is 4 different forms.</item>
        <item>The legendray falooda place, Badshah falooda is serving some signature faloodas since 1900s, before all of us were born! Head to this place and enjoy the legendary taste.</item>
        <item>This place started to be a small food stall turned in to a buzzing restaurant in the city. A big glass of tasty lassi topped with thick malai is their speciality.</item>



    </string-array>

    <string-array name="s_disc_four">


        <item>Classical music, classical vibes and a cup of tea, a perfect start of a day. One of the best places to explore over 40 tea varieties in the city.</item>
        <item>Blue Tokai, one of the new successful coffee outlets of Mumbai serves you freshly brewed coffee with delectable baked cookies and other treats.</item>
        <item>Gustoso, Italian style restaurant in Mumbai offers authentic Italian treat. This place have some great ratings for the pizza the offer with some lively musical ambience.</item>
        <item>Little Italy, as their name says they prove it with some authentic pastas on offer. The have a big menu card which includes Italian, Lebanese and Mexican cuisines.</item>
        <item>If you are hungry for a frankie, mark this place in your mind. Roti N provides spicy and yummy frankie in some serious quantity which might make you burp loudly! </item>
        <item>Students of Nationals and MMK have more than 75% attendance at this place. Jay Sandwich stall offers lip-smacking sandwiches at pocket friendly rates.</item>
        <item>Woodside Inn serves some best burgers in the city. Enjoy a tasty and heavy burger accompanied by lively music and interesting fact is - it is open til 2 AM.</item>
        <item>Appetite Momos at Thane is where you get a wide range of momos. Their menu card is a-z of momos. From Vegetarian Momos to Paneer Achari Momos they have it all!</item>
        <item>This place is light on pocket when compared with the quality of food they serve. Peco Peco is where you will start visiting occasionally if you visit once.</item>
        <item>If you are looking for a place to chill after a stressful day at the office, Hitchi it is! It has a nice and cozy ambience and you will love their crispy and spicy chinese bhel.</item>
        <item>Fat Five Monks brings to you the finest of South East Asian cuisines. You can have some best noodles in the city at this place along with wide variety of salads and juices.</item>
        <item>If you are a fan of authentic chinese cuisine, Mainland China is your destination. They serve high quality chinese food in fabulous atmosphere around.</item>
        <item>Chilli and Onion restaurant is the right location if you worry about you pocket. They offer some authentic Asian cuisine at affordable rates. Do try their soup.</item>
        <item>Amar Juice Center, what\'s in a name? This place happens to be one of the most popular pav bhaji outlets of Mumbai. Here you get your favorite pav bhaji within few minutes!</item>
        <item>Vinay Health Home, it seems like a chemist outlet but it is not. This place takes utmost care of hygiene and your health while serving some delicious authentic Maharashtrian food.</item>
        <item>Hygiene and cleanliness is primary goal at Gokhale Upahar Griha. They have open to view kitchen to show the hygiene they maintain and the quality food they serve.</item>
        <item>Paratha lovers if you need some change and variety in your favourite food this is your place. Khasiyat serves lip smacking wide variety of parathas at affordable rates.</item>
        <item>Don\'t make a mistake of judging the place on its looks and decor, Shree Chole Bhature serves some real gold when you talk about food at this place. Don\'t judge a book by cover!</item>
        <item>Serving typical North Indian and Punjabi food, Pratap Da Dhaba is where you should rush to if your soul is craving for some authentic dal khichdi with achar and papad.</item>
        <item>Kutumbsakhi is common man\'s eatery founded by a NGO to support married house wives to earn some income. The pohe they serve has some genuine and homely taste.</item>
        <item>Being in this business for more then 30 years, Aaswad serves mouth-watering Mahrashtrian and South Indian cuisines at the most affordable rates. Checkout their zunka bhakar. </item>
        <item>This 20 year old family run business, Graduate Vada Pav is one of the iconic vada pav location of Mumbai. Enjoy a Graduate Vada Pav with wide varieties of chutneys they offer.</item>
        <item>Heaven for vegetarian foodies, Soam has a wide variety of vegetarian snacks and sweets. One of the many other things that stand out here is their crispy and cheesy Samosas.</item>
        <item>Delhi Highway, you might feel you are somewhere in Delhi if you are in this restaurant. The raj kachori they serve has the \'Delhi Wali Feeling\'. Try it to believe it!</item>
        <item>To taste authentic Kutchi Dabeli you don\'t need to go to Gujrat when it is so close to you. The Dilkhush Dabeli in Vile Parle West serves delicious dabeli at pocket friendly rates.</item>
        <item>Is it possible to get 8 different varieties of dhokla at one place? Yes nothing is impossible when Rajubhai Dhoklawala is here. They have experimented and come up with some delights.</item>
        <item>D. Damodar Mithaiwala serves great quality Indian sweets made with pure ghee and some mouth-watering snacks. Check out some pakodas, the quality and taste is just perfect.</item>
        <item>You might be knowing this place for the gulab jamun they serve but you will like to know that this iconic location also serves icy cool and spicy pani puris in the city.</item>
        <item>Popular since 1875, Vithal Family Restaurant And Bar is where you should head to if you are craving for a tempting bhel. They serve other food items too but the bhel stands out.</item>
        <item>Kunj Vihar, best place to munch on healthy chat with some interesting taste. The dahi puri you get here is awesome along with other chat delights you get at this place.</item>
        <item>If you are vegetarian foodie you are definitely going to love this place with lot of vegetarian delights on offer. Kailash Parbat is very popular for some mouth-watering chats.</item>
        <item>If you are vegetarian foodie you are definitely going to love this place with lot of vegetarian delights on offer. Kailash Parbat is very popular for some mouth-watering chats.</item>
        <item>Khau Gali in Ghatkopar has many food stalls from chinese to desi food. But it is incomplete without chat stalls. The dahi vada you get at this place is lip smacking.</item>
        <item>You don\'t need to go to Chennai to taste some lip smacking South Indian food. Cafe Madras, stands out when it comes to eating some authentic South Indian dishes.</item>
        <item>One of the oldest South Indian eateries of Mumbai, Hotel Ram Ashraya is the place you should head to if you are craving to have some authentic idli in the city.</item>
        <item>Matunga has many South Indian outlets, but each of them have signature recipes. Here at Sharada Bhavan the upma you get has unbeatable taste, authentic medu vada!.</item>
        <item>This popular South Indian eatery in Mumbai, is know for the authentic South Indian dishes they make. The milky upma they serve is one of the best upma you don\'t get it anywhere else.</item>
        <item>Matunga has many South Indian outlets, but each of them have signature recipes. Here at Sharada Bhavan the upma you get has unbeatable taste, authentic utappa made at its best.</item>
        <item>Being in this business for more then 30 years, Aaswad serves mouth-watering Mahrashtrian and South Indian cuisines at the most affordable rates. Checkout their puran poli.</item>
        <item>Established 70 years ago, Adarsh Mithai Mandir is well known modak point of Mumbai. A wide array of mouth- watering modaks are up for display at this place, don\'t get confused!</item>
        <item>Gajar Ka Halwa is what you should look for if you are at The Indian Affair. They serve some authentic Mughalai cuisines along with mouth watering gajar ka halwa.</item>
        <item>J.J. Jalebi House gives you some mouth watering hot and fresh jalebi in the city. They taste each and every food item here and quality is maintained so you get the best.</item>
        <item>Brijawsi Bengali Sweets has a long menu card and a long queue. They offer a wide range of bengali sweets which are superb in taste and best in quality. Sweet lovers note down!</item>
        <item>Another place to enjoy some seriously sweet and tasty gulab jamuns in the city, Champaji Gulab Jamun House  will give you mouth melting gulab jamuns made in desi ghee.</item>
        <item>Where\'s My Cone, well you might find it at this ice cream outlet in Mumbai. They serve wide range of ice cream flavours and they can deliver at your home too!</item>
        <item>Himalaya, no you don\'t need to go to Himalaya when we have it in Mumbai. It is a small vegetarian joint and they serve some genuinely tasty kulfis in this city.</item>
        <item>This midnight meal of Mumbaikars can be found at Shalimar Cool Point. Shalimar is where you get a blast of sweetness in your mouth with some tasty falooda flavours.</item>
        <item>Parsi Dairy Farm offers creamy and pure lassi, the quality which you get here is unmatched.Established around 1917, this place also offers other high quality dairy items.</item>



    </string-array>

    <string-array name="s_disc_five">

        <item>This tea house is quite quirky just like its name. It is known for its cool ambiance and games that you can play as you wait for your hot piping tea and snacks.</item>
        <item>A place basked with positivity and liveliness, Garde Manger Cafe is where you get a cup of energetic coffee. This place is quite popular in Mumbai for its homely ambience and coffee.</item>
        <item>Pizza Express is where you can build you own pizza from base to toppings. They offer some authentic and mouth-watering pizzas in the city, which you won\'t find anywhere else.</item>
        <item>Their menu card starts with Classic Macaroni and ends with Cheese to Grilled Veg Spaghetti. With a huge range of pastas, best thing is you can also toss veggies of your choice.</item>
        <item>Ideal spot for a quick bite of divine and mouth-watering variety of frankies at the heart of the city. You won\'t see frankies in their menu card, as they call it Naan Roll here..</item>
        <item>This sweet and snack parlour in Powai is where you get iconic sandwich in the city. Specially known for grilled and toast sandwich, the cheese toppings on it turns it into gold.</item>
        <item>This place is known for it\'s creativity when it comes to burgers. They are very unique when we talk about burgers. You get some twist in the taste of burgers and burger names as well!</item>
        <item>Bhukka Sher as their name says, this is the right place to fill your empty stomach with a range of mouth-watering momos. One of the few places in the city who serve tandoori momos.</item>
        <item>Slurp and Burp outlet in Borivali is specialist in serving American Fast Food, but it is quite interesting to know that the chinese bhel you get here is unbeatable in taste.</item>
        <item>If you want to load your stomach with good amount of tasty food at affordable rates Dynasty is the right location to check out. It is a small place but the noodles will make you mad.</item>
        <item>Hakka Express brings you your favourite noodles at your doorstep. The best part about this eatery is they offer you wide range of noodles at extremely affordable prices.</item>
        <item>This place is one of the oldest bakeries in Bandra, a small eatery in some disguised location. But wait don\'t judge this place before you try some delectable snacks.</item>
        <item>South Mumbai folks are well aware of this gem, located in Shivaji Park Oven Fresh serves Mexican Italian cuisines at extremely pocket friendly rates.</item>
        <item>Shabri is a pretty good place to have tasty pav bhaji. Ambience is not that fancy but the pav bhaji they serve is class! The sitting is good and the food served is worth every penny.</item>
        <item>New Anand Bhuvan is one of the oldest Misal Joints located in South Mumbai. This place is quite popular for some genuine Marashtrian food. The Misal is super spicy!</item>
        <item>Established in 2007, Girgaon Katta, one of the authentic Marathi restaurants of Mumbai serves lip smaking Marathi food with pride being light on your pocket.</item>
        <item>If you are tired of eating the same paratha, it is time to experience the same food with western style. Paratha Mantra is where you get fusion parathas. Check out this place for a change!</item>
        <item>VIG Refreshments, a dhaba style Punjabi food location offers delicious chole bhature in the city. This location is difficult to find but its popularity will get you there.</item>
        <item>If you are quite serious about your health and still want to eat something delicious, Tipsy Terrace is the right place for you. What is more healthy and tasty then a multigrain khichdi!</item>
        <item>Vinay Health Home, it seems like a chemist outlet but it is not. This place takes utmost care of hygiene and your health while serving some delicious authentic Maharashtrian food.</item>
        <item>A simple and homely place for all the Maharashtrian food lovers, Prakash has maintained it\'s quality and taste over last few decades. Prakash\'s Zunka Bhakar is amazing.</item>
        <item>The Parleshwar Vada Pav Samrat, is quick food stop especially for the college students. This is the right location to grab a quick vada pav if you are some where in Vile Parle.</item>
        <item>B. Merwan is the only place where you get this kind of Samosa in the city. The samosa you get here is filled with mawa unlike the regular samosa you have.</item>
        <item>Elco, highly rated chat location of Mumbai visited by bollywood celebrities in the city. A perfect place to enjoy lip smacking raj kachori with proper hygiene and quality.</item>
        <item>Early bird catches the worm! This phrase is quite applicable at Joshi\'s  Dabeli House, head to this place early as possible to get something before they are completely sold out.</item>
        <item>Gaurav Sweets and Namkeen is where you get some tasty Gujrati snacks at great price without compromising the hygiene. They are professional when it comes to making dhoklas.</item>
        <item>A certified location to taste the iconic food of Mumbai \'The Vadapav\'. Standing strong since last 35 years, Ashok Vada Pav also serves hot and crispy pakode - unbeatable in taste.</item>
        <item>The Punjab Sweet House, authentic Punjabi restaurant going good since many decades turns out to be a good place to check out with your family and enjoy some best pani puri.</item>
        <item>Elco, highly rated chat location of Mumbai visited by bollywood celebrities in the city. A perfect place to enjoy lip smacking bhelpuri with proper hygiene and quality.</item>
        <item>Sai Veg World, more than a typical udipi joint, apart from their simple South Indian food they also serve Punjabi and Chinese cuisine but the chat they offer stands out of all.</item>
        <item>A sev puri garnished with lush green coriander and crispy sev makes this special and worth going. Jalram Snacks is one of the best chats  because of the uniqueness they bring in!</item>
        <item>They have build their position and standards when it comes to serving good quality food with good quantity. With great service and great ambience they offer great ragda pattice.</item>
        <item>One of the oldest South Indian eateries of Mumbai, Hotel Ram Ashraya is the place you should head to if you are craving to have some authentic dahi vada in the city.</item>
        <item>Fusion dosas are common these days, but Nandu Dosa takes this concept to next level by serving Manchurian dosa, Khakra dosa, Salad dosa and what not. The dosa creativity place.</item>
        <item>This popular South Indian eatery in Mumbai, is know for the authentic South Indian dishes they make. The idli is of top notch and probably which you won\'t get anywhere else.</item>
        <item>Dakshinayan, a South Indian restaurant in Juhu serves authentic South Indian dishes in you plate. With unbeatable food, this restaurant is light on your pocket too!</item>
        <item>Dakshinayan, a South Indian restaurant in Juhu serves authentic South Indian dishes in you plate. With unbeatable food, this restaurant is light on your pocket too!</item>
        <item>This popular South Indian eatery in Mumbai, is know for the authentic South Indian dishes they make. The utappa is of top notch and probably which you won\'t get anywhere else.</item>
        <item>Mi Marathi is authentic restaurant to get into a Marathi Mood and Marathi Food. However the best part is menu card is in Marathi and waiter will speak in Marathi!</item>
        <item>Established in 1921, one of the legandary modak outlets in the city Panshikar serves a huge range of modak from fruity variations to dry fruit modaks, all best in taste.</item>
        <item>Taste of Punjab has a wide range of North Indian cuisines and pretty ambience. One thing you should fix in your mind is to have a gajar ka halwa every time you come here.</item>
        <item>Harilal Kashidas Bhajiwala, is one of legendary shops which is 8 decades old. Their name might say bhajiwala but they are popularly known for fresh jalebi and fafdas they serve.</item>
        <item>Established around 100 years ago, one of the oldest Bengali Sweet joints in Mumbai , Bhaishankar offers the best quality Bengali Sweets. Their flavoured rasgulla, hats off!.</item>
        <item>Known for their creamy lassi, M. M. Mithaiwala is a quite reputed brand serving quality sweets in the city. Their gulab jamuns are often underestimated, give some respect!</item>
        <item>Apsara Icecream serves premium hand churned icecream with wide range of fruity and dry-fruit flavours. They are known for the quality and taste since last 40 years.</item>
        <item>Gokul Icecream is a popular name. This place is quite interesting when it comes to decor and ambience. The ice creams they serve are made in traditional home-style manner.</item>
        <item>You can close your eyes and point your finger anywhere in their menu card, you won\'t be disappointed. Order anything, they make it the best. Be it juices, shakes or faloodas!</item>
        <item>At Oye Teri in Borivali you will find their menu card filled with a range of kulchas. But what you will love the most is their awesome classic lassi with a twist of pineapple.</item>






    </string-array>

</resources>

